[Music]
[音楽]
our live recording is a trusted only to
私たちのライブ録音は
solid-state drives by Kingston
キングストンのソリッドステートドライブ
technology revive your computer with
テクノロジーがコンピューターを蘇らせます
improved performance and reliability
パフォーマンスと信頼性の向上
over traditional hard drives with
従来のハードドライブと
Kingston SSDs category 5 TV streams live
キングストンSSDカテゴリ5のテレビストリームがライブ
with Telestream Wirecast and nimble
Telestream Wirecastと軽快な
screamer tune in every week on roku cody
roku codyの毎週のスクリーマーチューン
and other HLS video players for local
およびその他のローカル向けHLSビデオプレーヤー
show times visit category 5 TV welcome
上映時間はカテゴリ5のテレビへようこそ
to the show everybody it's so great to
みんなにショーをするのはとても素晴らしい
have you here have you ever had a hard
ここにいますか
drive crash bro yes my hard drive failed
ドライブクラッシュ仲間はい私のハードドライブが故障しました
this past week I'm filled filled um no I
この一週間、私はいっぱいになった
didn't have a backup but that's me in my
バックアップはありませんでしたが、それは私です
scenario I didn't need a backup because
シナリオバックアップが必要なかったのは、
I don't store anything on my hard drive
ハードドライブには何も保存しません
oh ok so I'm ok mm-hmm my hard drive
大丈夫だから大丈夫だよ
failed there was no backup oh there was
失敗したバックアップはありませんでした
like seven years of photos see my life
7年間の写真が私の人生を見るように
is about central management of data so
データの集中管理についてです
like this is how I'm able to use like a
これは私がどのように使用できるかです
pine Book Pro to do video and yeah we
パイン・ブック・プロがビデオを制作します
talked about cells I'm remoted in
私が遠隔地にいる細胞について話しました
through a VPN connection to a massive
VPN接続を介して大規模な
server that has I I scuzzy access to
IIのあいまいなアクセス権を持つサーバー
massive storage so I don't need any kind
大容量のストレージなので、何も必要ありません
of storage on my devices so when my hard
私のデバイス上のストレージの
drive failed as I failed it it didn't
私はそれが失敗しなかったので、ドライブは失敗しました
take any of my data with it it just was
それと私のデータのいずれかを取ります
a bit of an inconvenience I had to put
ちょっと不便だった
in a new drive and and get back up and
新しいドライブに入れて、戻って
running get everything reinstalled but
実行してすべてを再インストールしますが、
what was a little frightening about this
これについて少し怖かった
particular failure uh-huh that I have
私が持っている特定の失敗
never encountered in my entire career as
私のキャリア全体で遭遇したことはない
a computer technician in my entire life
私の人生のコンピューター技術者
is that when I walked in to my office
私がオフィスに入ったとき
there was a stench of melted electronics
溶けたエレクトロニクスの悪臭がありました
Oh No
大野
oh I don't have very good photos but
ああ、あまり良い写真はありませんが
what I have I will give you my hard
私が持っているもの私はあなたに私のハードを与えます
drive caught on fire overnight oh yes
ドライブは一晩で火事に遭いました
so within the chassis of my computer
だから私のコンピューターのシャーシ内
which is like an aluminium yeah case
これはアルミ製ケースのようなものです
there was a fire Wow
火がありました
yeah so when you think about so and then
そうそうあなたがそう考える時
I'm thinking oh my goodness all the time
私はいつも私の良さを考えています
I've never seen this happen before oh
これが起こるのを見たことがない
wow and there's nothing that I have ever
うわー、私が今まで持っていたものは何もありません
done that should have caused that
それはそれを引き起こしたはずだった
there's no there's nothing that I did to
私がやったことは何もない
do that there's no there was no dust
ほこりがなかったことをしないでください
buildup
築き上げる
no the computer is perfectly clean under
いいえ、コンピューターは完全にきれいです
my desk and is as never moved it's
私の机は動かない
statically set up and it just was it was
静的に設定されただけでした
a cheap SSD I think and it literally
私が思う安いSSDとそれは文字通り
caught on fire inside the chassis so the
シャーシ内で火災が発生したため、
fire was contained the computer was ok
火が含まれていたコンピュータは大丈夫だった
thankfully but stunts like a beast no
ありがたいことに獣のようなスタント
dough for about three days but the drive
約3日間の生地が、ドライブ
itself was so baked did you contacts no
それ自体はとても焼かれていた
no I replaced it with a good Kingston
いいえ、私はそれを良いキングストンに置き換えました
heart yeah yeah I did and reinstall my
心そうそう私はやったと私の再インストール
stuff and you know I'm back up and
ものとあなたは私がバックアップしている知っている
running in a few hours come you didn't
数時間で走ります
do this the first time but it really did
初めてこれを行うが、本当にやった
make me think about all those times that
そのすべての時間について私に考えさせます
I've thought about doing like wooden
私は木製のようにすることを考えました
builds like maybe it was a really good
多分それは本当に良かったようなビルド
thing that my computer chassis was made
私のコンピューターのシャーシが作られたこと
of aluminium yes maybe that and and
アルミニウムのはい多分それと
fairly airtight to the point where not a
ではない点までかなり気密
whole lot of oxygen can get in once once
一度に全部の酸素が入ります
it's expelled right yeah so like the
それはまさにそう追放されています
burning didn't affect any of the other
燃焼は他のどれにも影響しませんでした
components no because it was in the in
コンポーネントなし
the drive tray so it was contained
それが含まれていたので、ドライブトレイ
within the tray so so the tray itself
トレイ内なので、トレイ自体が
actually had some plastic components as
実際にいくつかのプラスチック部品がありました
well those plastic components melted and
プラスチック部品が溶けて
dripped down Wow but the washburn it was
すごい落ちましたが、ウォッシュバーンは
like oh it was a fire it was a fire
ああ、それは火だった、それは火だった
inside the case of the hard drive yeah
ハードドライブのケースの中に
the SSD
SSD
and that's a crazy part is that it's an
そしてそれはクレイジーな部分であるということです
SSD like I I could see that maybe with
IIのようなSSDは、おそらく
you know traditional hard drive with my
あなたは私の伝統的なハードドライブを知っています
moving parts but an SSD to catch fire I
可動部品であるが、火災を起こすSSD
would be really proud if it was like I'm
私のようだったら本当に誇りに思う
moving parts thing like I worked that
私が働いたような可動部分の事
beast so I got it up to 15 billion rpm
獣なので、150億rpmまで上げました
that's rent
それは家賃です
nobody must have burnt for a while it
誰もしばらく燃やしたに違いない
was pretty bad so so you did you get
かなり悪かったので、あなたは
alerts
アラート
ah this is just my desktop computer I
ああ、これはちょうど私のデスクトップコンピュータです
didn't have names running monitoring on
監視を実行している名前がありませんでした
it or anything like that however because
それかそのようなもの
the board the it did make me think
ボードはそれを考えさせた
because the motherboard has USB ports on
マザーボードのUSBポートがオンになっているため
the motherboard yeah I think I might put
マザーボードは、私が置くかもしれないと思う
a temper device in my computer chassis
コンピューターのシャシーにあるテンパーデバイス
and a temper devices like a USB thermal
USBサーマルなどのテンパーデバイス
sensor we did do that
私たちがやったセンサー
so imagine putting that in and then I
それを想像して
could have gotten an alert from Nimes
ニームからアラートを受け取ったかもしれない
Linux that said hey your computer is a
あなたのコンピューターはちょっと
hundred and 40 degrees Celsius and would
摂氏百と40度と
you have been like a mistake that would
あなたは間違いのようでした
have been a little bit of a strange
少し奇妙なものでした
alert for sure however you can trust
確かに警告するが、信頼できる
MEMS that the data is accurate so then
データが正確であるMEMS
you would have gone to see it in action
あなたは実際にそれを見に行っていただろう
brought some marshmallows yeah but
マシュマロを持ってきました
thankfully it was contained because that
ありがたいことにそれが含まれていた
could have impacted the entire office
オフィス全体に影響を与えた可能性があります
yeah but doesn't it make you think about
ええ、でも考えさせてくれませんか
like all these like builds that I'm
私がしているようなすべてのこれらのようなビルドのように
doing and and some of them made of
し、それらのいくつかはで作られた
cardboard so I'm really kind of
段ボールなので、私は本当に
rethinking the materials that I use for
私が使用する材料を再考する
my builds and and you know I think about
私のビルドとあなたは私が考えることを知っています
kks be cases for for single board
kksはシングルボードの場合
computers and how they're like solid
コンピューターとその固体の様子
steel mm-hmm then and fabricated steel
鋼mm-hmmその後、加工鋼
and that just says quality to me and
そしてそれは私に品質を言うだけで、
like that's gonna it's gonna protect me
それは私を守るつもりだ
an event of like a short circuit or
短絡のようなイベントまたは
something like that I don't know what
そのような何か私は知らない
happened to the drive it was like an
ドライブに起こったように
internal thing I've never had a hard
私が苦労したことのない内部的なこと
drive catch matter no matter how are
どのようにキャッチ問題を駆動します
supplies I haven't I've never I've never
物資は持ってない
had a fire like that yeah yeah I was the
あのような火があった
computer that I built on four years ago
4年前に構築したコンピューター
six months in all sudden and I'm like
突然半年で
what is that
それは何ですか
spell yeah and then I went down with a
ええ、それから私は
computer and I realize oh it's smoked
コンピューターと私はそれが喫煙だとわかります
sure but I've burnt capacitors I've had
確かに、私は持っていたコンデンサを燃やしました
things burst yeah but I'm talking this
物事はええが、私はこれを話している
caught on fire like literally I was not
文字通り私はそうではなかったように燃えた
from heat this was like a short circuit
熱からこれは短絡のようでした
in the power lines or something whew
送電線または何かで
within the drive the crazy stuff so so
ドライブ内でクレイジーなものをそうそう
now I mean hey I've never seen it happen
今私はそれが起こるのを見たことがないね
before but now I know it could happen
前に、しかし今、私はそれが起こる可能性があることを知っています
really it actually did happen - Robbie
本当にそれが実際に起こった-ロビー
what are the stats I want I think we
私が望む統計は何ですか
should all try to simulate it make it
すべてシミュレートしようとする必要があります
happen oh yeah I wonder if there's a kid
ああ、そうそう子供がいるのかな
like there is some data as to what could
何ができるかについてのデータがあるように
cause an SSD to light on fire what's on
SSDを点灯させます
the inside I don't think it's a very
内部は私はそれが非常にだとは思わない
common thing
よくあること
what what's on the inside of it what is
その中身は何ですか
that you've got a PCB circuit board with
あなたがPCB回路基板を持っていること
with with memory modules yeah
メモリモジュールを使用して
essentially and and some resistors and
本質的におよびいくつかの抵抗器と
all kinds of little circuits and stuff
あらゆる種類の小さな回路やもの
but so something in there no there's no
しかし、そこに何かありません
moving parts and some something in there
可動部品とその中の何か
short-circuited I think and maybe like
ショートしたと思う
12 volt hit something else and decided
12ボルトが他の何かに当たって決定した
to explode and catch I don't know the
爆発してキャッチするために私は知らない
interesting is that it happened when you
おもしろいのは、あなたが
weren't in the office because if it
オフィスにいなかったのは
happened while you were in the office
あなたがオフィスにいる間に起こった
you might have taken a while for you to
しばらく時間がかかったかもしれません
figure out I might have been like okay
大丈夫だったかもしれない
my computer's on fire like you see what
あなたが見るように私のコンピューターは燃えている
a smell died oh yeah brutal yeah you
臭いが消えた
might have ruined your computer with
お使いのコンピューターを台無しにした可能性があります
like a fire extinguisher at that point
その時点で消火器のような
maybe yeah it's probably good probably
たぶんそれはおそらく良いでしょう
good well but an electrical fire
良いが、電気火災
contained within an aluminum boxes yeah
ええ、アルミの箱の中に
hopefully pretty safe was in one of my
うまくいけば、私の中にかなり安全だった
wooden chassis why do I smell charred
木製のシャーシ
Hickory Wow speaking of burnt have you
ヒッコリーワウ焼けと言えばあなたがいる
tried any healthy foods lately I am
最近健康的な食べ物を試しました
always trying healthy foods Jeff because
いつもヘルシーな食べ物を試そうジェフ
I'm learning from the technology that
私は技術から学んでいます
I've invested in now my budget was a
私は今予算に投資しました
hundred bucks as you know so a few weeks
ご存知のように数百ドル
ago we started looking at the various
前に私たちは様々な
technologies like my fitness tracker
私のフィットネストラッカーのような技術
like my smart scale that allow me to
私のできるスマートスケールのように
educate myself about my health
自分の健康について自分自身を教育する
to be able to lose some weight
体重を減らすことができる
inevitably as kind of a side effect of
必然的に副作用の一種として
that and I have consistent so so
それと私はそう一貫している
whenever I tell you how much I've lost
どれだけ失ったかを言うたびに
it's it's only based on consistency so
一貫性のみに基づいているので、
if I if I hit seven point six pounds
もし私が7ポイント6ポンドを打ったら
loss and then I went back to six point
損失し、6ポイントに戻りました
I'm gonna I'm not gonna tell you seven
私はあなたに7つを話すつもりはないつもりです
but I've been consistently beyond of the
しかし、私は一貫して
seven pounds mark now so another couple
今7ポンドのマークなので、別のカップル
pounds since last week and I've only
先週からポンドと私は
been doing it for a month and it's just
1ヶ月間それをやっていて、それはただ
by educating myself but part of that
自分自身を教育することによって、その一部
Jeff is yeah eating a little well eating
ジェフは少し食べてうん
healthy but I've cut carbs as much as I
健康ですが、私は炭水化物をできるだけ減らしました
can from my diet because I learned about
私が知ったので食事からできる
the fact that I'm burning carbs instead
代わりに炭水化物を燃やしているという事実
of burning fat and it's working as
脂肪燃焼の
really it actually is working so yeah I
本当にそれは実際に働いているので
did like I've been using cauliflower
カリフラワーを使っているように
instead of rice so ground up cauliflower
ご飯の代わりにカリフラワーをすりつぶします
yeah it's actually delicious so yeah so
ええ、実際に美味しいので
and it's like a rice substitute but
そして、それは米代用品のようなものですが
there's no carbs so but it's just like a
炭水化物がないので、それはちょうどのようなものです
plate of vegetable instead of rice you
ご飯の代わりに野菜のプレート
can cut up some green onions oh yes
ねぎを切ることができます
mushrooms and stuff like that I would
キノコやそのようなもの
I'll have pizza once a like I get a
ピザを手に入れたら
cheap day once a week so I took my
週に一度安い日なので
daughter for her pizza and we had like a
彼女のピザの娘と私たちのような
cheese pizza and that's fun I also have
チーズピザとそれも私が持っている楽しみです
started so now I'm at that point where
始めたので、今私はその時点で
I've kind of not plateaued I'm still
私はまだ停滞していません
losing weight fairly consistently but
かなり一貫して体重を減らすが、
fairly slowly so one of the things in we
かなりゆっくりなので、私たちの中の一つ
have a Biggest Loser channel on discord
不協和音で最大の敗者チャンネルを持っている
and Marshman had mentioned that one of
マーシュマンは
the things I can do to kind of
私ができること
accelerate things is to to sustain
物事を加速することは維持することです
exercise in such a way that okay like if
次のような大丈夫な方法で運動する
I run up the stairs yeah my heart rate
私は階段を駆け上がった
gets going but then it's it settles back
行くが、それはそれが戻って落ち着いている
down but right I'm done well so do
ダウンしますが、私はうまくやったのでそうします
things that are gonna sustain a little
少し持続するもの
bit more exercise essentially so I'm not
基本的にもう少し運動するので
doing anything out of the ordinary like
普通ではないことをする
I'm not really changing my life or
私は人生を本当に変えていない
anything because I've got to be within
内にいなければならないから
reason for the way that I live yeah but
ええ、私が生きている理由
you know I gave my my 12 year old a
私は私の12歳を与えた知っています
piggyback ride at while we were at
でおんぶ
Walmart it works
ウォルマートは動作します
I'm I'm looking and I'm like holy cow I
私は探しています、そして私は聖なる牛のようです
burned a lot of calories doing that I
それをしてカロリーをたくさん燃やした
actually kind of started to get sore
実際に痛みを感じ始めた
legs doing that because like he's 12
彼が12歳だから
years old he's a big big guy and and so
彼は大きくて大きい男だから
for him it was a lot of fun it was a
彼にとってはとても楽しかったです
great time for me it was like this is a
私にとっては最高の時間でした
great great way to sustain that kind of
そのような種類を維持するための素晴らしい素晴らしい方法
heart rate so that was something and
心拍数です
then I took my youngest who's nine I
それから私は私の一番下の9人です
took him skating last night so we just
昨夜彼をスケートに連れて行ったので
we found an outdoor skating rink here in
ここで屋外スケートリンクを見つけました
Barrie Ontario and we strapped on the
バリー・オンタリオと私たちは
skates for the first time in a couple of
のカップルで初めてスケート
years nice and and we skated for an hour
素敵な年で、1時間スケートをしました
and 15 minutes or so yeah it was fun and
そして15分かそこらは楽しかったです
for him again so it for for the kids
彼のために、それは子供たちのために
it's like this is great daddy time
これは素晴らしいパパの時間のようです
mm-hmm for dad it's great bad child time
お父さんにとってはうーん、それは素晴らしい悪い子の時間です
but also at the same time I'm I'm I've
同時に私は私も
got that kind of side motive of am doing
やっているというそのような動機を得た
things with the kids that are trying to
しようとしている子供たちとの事
get me to be more physically active as a
として物理的にアクティブになる
computer geek because I'm for your
私はあなたのためだからコンピュータオタク
children that this fun activity stuff is
この楽しいアクティビティは
actually fun right yeah yeah yeah if
ええええええ
you're like I'll go outside and play and
あなたは私が外に出て遊びます
you don't do it yourself
あなたは自分でそれをしません
it's not as much fun as if you know
知っているほど楽しくない
dad's out there actually sure playing
お父さんは実際に遊んでいる
around and I was also surprised like
周りと私も驚きました
something like finding an outdoor
アウトドアを見つけるようなもの
skating rink that the city maintains
市が維持しているスケートリンク
like they have a Zamboni at their
彼らは彼らにザンボニを持っているように
outdoor skate skating rink like this is
このような屋外スケートリンクは
serious
真面目な
real-deal skating and it's free which
本物のスケートとそれは無料です
was also tax dollars pay for it so you
税金も払っていたので
just go and strap on your skates and go
スケート靴を履いて行くだけ
and skate as long as you want it's open
あなたがそれが開いている限り、スケート
till 10:00 p.m. so for me it was like
午後10時までだから私にとっては
this is a really really cheap outing
これは本当に安い外出です
cost us nothing to go out so that was
外出に費用はかかりませんでした
fantastic so you're living healthier I
素晴らしいので、あなたはより健康に生きていますI
quite frankly I'm just not caring too
率直に言って、私も気にしない
much right about now but I will say fine
今すぐにでも大丈夫です
it's very busy weekend yeah and on
週末はとても忙しいです
Saturday and Sunday my watch rewarded me
土曜日と日曜日に時計が報われた
for beating my daily activity goals I
私の毎日の活動目標を破って
was like yeah because I had stuff to do
やりたいことがあったから
in a house to clean there you go but it
そこを掃除する家に行く
was good I will say though I think my
良かったと思うけど
steps are lower today last week I'm at
先週、今日は歩数が減りました
878 steps aside you have a car
車を持っている878ステップ
got forty five hundred seventy five
四百五百七十五
hundred so that's lower than last week
100なので、先週よりも低くなります
lower last week last week that was in
先週より低い先週
competition well they cheat did you know
競争はよくごまかしました
I don't cheat
私はカンニングしません
well no we are the company today there
まあ、私たちは今日の会社です
has been some discussion and discord on
いくつかの議論と不一致がありました
what cheating really is I play video
不正行為とは何ですか
games and it ups my step count I know
ゲームとそれは私が知っている私のステップカウントアップ
we're saying you're using this as a way
これを方法として使用していると言っています
to main like I'm doing with the
私がやっているようにメインに
piggyback rides
おんぶ
I maintain that it doesn't feel like
私はそれがそう感じないことを維持します
cheating to me did you use activity
私にごまかしはアクティビティを使用しましたか
manipulation to when you're noticed I
あなたが気づいたときの操作
didn't know okay so what did you do this
大丈夫知りませんでしたので、あなたはこれを何をしましたか
week oh this week I beat Crimson Fang
今週は今週、私はクリムゾンファングを倒しました
tell us about it okay that's like a real
大丈夫、それは本物のようです
workout yes well in virtual yeah as you
あなたと同じように仮想でそうです
say you have to clarify though what
あなたは何を明確にする必要があると言います
crimson Fang is okay so I have an a5 and
深紅の牙は大丈夫なので、私はa5を持っています
HTC vive and I play a game called
HTC viveと呼ばれるゲームをプレイします
knockout League so in that game there's
リーグをノックアウトするので、そのゲームには
a series of competitors that you fight
あなたが戦う一連の競争相手
against and I boxing I was in a boxing
に対して、私はボクシング私はボクシングにいた
match and they are tough they're beasts
マッチし、彼らは獣ですタフです
because they're not based in reality
彼らは現実に基づいていないので
they can do things that I cannot do oh
彼らは私ができないことをできる
and I was really stuck on Crimson Fang
そして、私は本当に深紅の牙に引っかかった
like for a long time because she wears
彼女が着ているので長い間好き
this mask and if you punched you slow
このマスクとあなたがあなたを遅くパンチした場合
the mascal bite you
マスカルはあなたを噛みます
oh dear and I was and just like real box
ああ、私は本当の箱のようだった
that's on fire based on reality the mask
それは現実のマスクに基づいて燃えています
bite you and Mike Tyson didn't need a
あなたをかむとマイクタイソンは必要ありませんでした
mask the foot and the fights last six
足をマスクし、最後の6戦
minutes and oftentimes when I lose I
分、そしてしばしば私が私を失うとき
lose like at the 5 minutes and 30
5分30秒のように失う
seconds so I don't have that staying
秒なので、私はその滞在がありません
power for the whole six minute round
6分間のラウンド全体のパワー
yeah okay so I had to really work myself
はい、大丈夫です
up to the cardio of a six minute fight I
6分間の戦いの有酸素運動まで
don't understand how they do rounds of
彼らがどのようにラウンドするのか理解していない
this against real competitors it was
これは本当の競争相手に対して
intense anyway so my next opponent is
とにかく激しいので、次の相手は
gonna be a long way off so was this like
ずっと先に行くので、こんな感じでした
exclusively a cardiovascular kind of
心血管系の
like yes like do you feel it in your in
はいのようにあなたはあなたの中でそれを感じますか
your in your everything no there's no
あなたのすべてにあなたはいません
there's no physical interaction right
物理的な相互作用はありません
well you're holding onto the control
さて、あなたはコントロールを握っている
right not that they have a lot of weight
体重が多いというわけではありません
but you're also like swinging picking D
しかし、あなたはまた、スイングピッキングDのようなものです
king dodging so like it's a full-body
キングが身をかわすように
deal like it's gotta try this sometime
いつか試してみてください
you have to try it how long ago did she
どれくらい前に彼女がやったの？
build that computer two years ago a
そのコンピューターを2年前に構築し、
couple years where we're supposed to
私たちがするはずの数年
have like a next Wednesday very cool
来週の水曜日はとてもかっこいい
so however you decide I mean this is for
しかし、あなたはこれが
me as part of my kind of New Year's
私の新年の一部として私
resolution but my New Year's resolution
解像度が、私の新年の解像度
is really just to educate myself that's
本当に自分自身を教育することです
how that's my approach and I am finding
それは私のアプローチであり、私は見つけています
that by educating myself I'm learning
私は自分自身を教育することで学んでいること
more about how things work and I'm
物事の仕組みについての詳細と私は
losing weight I've lost over seven
体重が減りました
pounds in the past month which isn't
過去1か月のポンドではない
huge but for me I can see it in my face
巨大ですが、私にとっては私の顔にそれを見ることができます
I can feel it in my body and and I'm
体で感じることができて
excited about you know where I'm gonna
私がどこに行くのか知っているあなたに興奮
be six months from now I feel like I'll
今から6ヶ月後
be healthier yeah so will I pounds is
もっと健康になります
huge don't know don't be like it's not
巨大なわからない
huge that's huge
でかい
it's a it's a great achievement for sure
それは確かに素晴らしい成果です
ya know and I feel great about it I'm
知ってますよ、私はそれについて素晴らしい気分です
not I'm not downplaying that at all I'm
私はそれを軽視していません
just like it's not like I lost 20 pounds
20ポンドも減らなかったように
in a week no no I'm just seven pounds I
一週間でいやいや、私はたった7ポンドだよ
haven't done anything other than changed
変更された以外は何もしていません
just my knowledge that's what about 4%
ちょうど私の知識、それは約4％
for you seven pounds uh-huh don't make
あなたのために7ポンドええとしないでください
me do math today Jeff please don't say
今日私は数学をしますジェフは言ってはいけません
for me plate open pouch whatever
私にとっては何でもオープンポーチ
whatever it is for you I just encourage
それはあなたのためです
you to like check out the technologies
テクノロジーをご覧ください
that are available if you've ever had
あなたが持っていた場合に利用可能です
trouble with with if it's weight loss or
減量や
if it's like keeping the new year's
新年を守るようなものなら
resolution there's tech that's available
解像度は利用可能な技術があります
like the fitness tracker like that scale
そのスケールのようなフィットネストラッカーのような
that is encouraging me by giving the
それは与えることによって私を励ましています
information about like BMI and stuff
BMIなどに関する情報
that I didn't know about before my
私の前に知らなかったこと
metabolic age I've lost two years off my
代謝年齢私は私の2年を失った
off my medical baggage so I'm now two
荷物を預けて、2人になりました
years younger in the past month
過去1か月若い
so that's huge so those kinds of things
巨大だからそういうもの
are really good encouragement in the end
最後に本当に良い励ましです
they'll help you to be able to achieve
彼らはあなたが達成できるようにするのに役立ちます
the goals just by educating you and and
あなたを教育するだけで目標を達成し、
helping you to see how the things that
どのように物事を見るのに役立ちます
you choose to eat and do
あなたは食べてやることを選ぶ
are affecting your health so it's
健康に影響しているので
working for me so far so maybe it will
今のところ私のために働いているので
work for you to get into Biggest Loser
最大の敗者になるためにあなたのために働く
Biggest Loser on our discord channel so
不協和音チャンネルの最大の敗者
go on to category 5 TV join our discord
カテゴリ5のテレビに進みます
under interact and and you'll see
相互作用の下で、あなたが表示されます
biggest loser there it's pretty fun I
そこの最大の敗者はかなり楽しいです
really want to get into the future well
本当にうまく未来に乗りたい
we've got to take a break first Jeff and
ジェフと最初の休憩を取る必要があります
then when we get back Jeff has got
ジェフが戻ってきたら
something for you folks so stick around
皆さんのために
[Music]
[音楽]
I have three kids at home we all have
家には3人の子供がいます
devices my wife myself I've got a phone
妻が自分で携帯電話を持っている
in my pocket at all times except at
を除いて常に私のポケットに
night when I need to charge it mm-hmm my
充電する必要がある夜mm-hmm my
kids each have you know we have a
子供たちはそれぞれ、私たちが持っていることを知っています
variety of phones that the kids share
子供が共有するさまざまな携帯電話
for video games and for chatting and
ビデオゲームやチャットのために
things like that so there's always stuff
そのようなものなので、常にものがあります
hanging out of wall outlets ghom I've
壁コンセントからぶら下がっています
got a wall wart with a cable and people
ケーブルと人々で壁war贅を得た
fighting over hey he's using my charger
彼は私の充電器を使用しているちょっとねえと戦って
and yeah always it's just the way it is
ええ、いつもそうです
so Jeff you talked about a couple weeks
ジェフは数週間話しました
ago how you've come up with a solution
解決策を思いついた前に
for kind of centralizing your charging
充電を一元化するために
station and it really made me think and
駅とそれは本当に私に考えさせ、
I started looking and I found a pretty
私は探し始めました
fantastic device that that I think
私が思う素晴らしいデバイス
you're you're going to show us today
あなたは今日私たちを見せようとしている
cord yeah so I mean you're right I do
コードそうだから、私はあなたが正しいことを意味する
have another device it's not the G chord
Gコードではない別のデバイスがある
I bought it around Christmas time yeah
クリスマスの頃に買ったよ
and it is a six bank docking station
そしてそれは6つの銀行のドッキングステーションです
that allows the kids to place their
それは子供たちが彼らを配置することができます
phones but we have again three kids but
電話ですが、3人の子供がいますが、
between them they have their old phones
彼らの間に彼らは古い携帯電話を持っています
and their new phones right yeah they
そして彼らの新しい携帯電話は
don't want to give up the old phones
古い電話をあきらめたくない
because well my minecraft files are not
私のMinecraftのファイルは
that old
あの古い
yeah so all in all I think there's like
ええ、全部全部で
six phones and two tablets Center and
6台の電話と2台のタブレットセンター
it's like there's same deal Chargers
同じ取引充電器があるようです
everywhere and one goes missing and like
どこでも行方不明になります
this is ridiculous
ばかげてる
but we also had the issue of they were
しかし、彼らの問題もありました
sneaking them at night I'm like we need
夜にそれらをこっそり私たちが必要なようだ
a centralized location where it's like I
私のような中央の場所
know where they all are so we got this
それらがすべてどこにあるかを知っているので、私たちはこれを手に入れました
charging port and they all just sit
充電ポートと彼らはすべて座っている
there and so yeah it's been it's been
そこにあるので、そうです
great and so does this have that feature
素晴らしいので、これにはその機能があります
where if the kids grab it after 9:00 it
子供が9時以降にそれをつかむ場合
zaps them nah no feature request that's
機能要求はありません
what I'm telling the kids if you touch
あなたが触れた場合、私は子供たちに言っていること
the phone after 9:00 while it's on the
午前9時以降の電話
charging station it will delete
充電ステーションは削除します
everything charging station sounds like
すべての充電ステーションのように聞こえます
a great idea for me because it puts
それは置くため、私にとって素晴らしいアイデア
everything in one place in it and it
そこにあるすべてのものとそれ
gets rid of all the cable clutter yes
はい、すべてのケーブルクラッターを取り除きます
can we see what you have here okay so
あなたがここに何があるかわかりますか？
this is from G chord it is a six port 10
これはGコードからのもので、6ポート10です
amp USB charging station now I will say
アンプUSB充電ステーション
right off the hop would caught me off
すぐに私を捕まえるだろう
guard from the boxes at the side that
その側のボックスからガード
says quad USB like but it's 6 port okay
クアッドUSBのようなが、それは大丈夫6ポートです
why is it quad USB it's because you've
なぜそれはクアッドUSBですか
got different types of USB so there's a
さまざまな種類のUSBが用意されているため、
there's three piece 8 pin there's two
3個の8ピンがあり、2個あります
piece micro USB and then one type see
ピースマイクロUSB、そして1つのタイプを参照してください
interestingly enough so my phone is Type
興味深いことに、私の電話はType
C but mine is the only one that's type c
Cしかし、私のものはタイプcの唯一のものです
within our household everything else is
私たちの家庭内では他のすべてが
USB micro although there is one Apple
USBマイクロ
device which uses the old Apple
古いAppleを使用するデバイス
interface so you came with some cables
あなたがいくつかのケーブルが付属しているので、インターフェイス
it does come okay but I'm gonna open
それは大丈夫ですが、私は開くつもりです
this up so I'm just gonna slice through
これで私はちょうどスライスするつもりです
that and place that over here so what do
それをここに置きます
we have in here starts with I like that
私たちがここに持っているのは私が好き
it's ten amps so you've got like one
それは10アンペアですので、あなたは1のようになっています
cable going to the outlet and you don't
ケーブルはコンセントに行きますが
have to have like a whole bunch of
全体の束のようにする必要があります
charges right it's just one thing nice
正しく充電するだけでいいのです
alright so it is a 6 port or 6 channel
申し分なく、それは6ポートまたは6チャンネルです
so alright to start with here's your
ここから始めて大丈夫です
various cables yeah okay so these are oh
さまざまなケーブルは大丈夫だから、これらはああです
so it came with little short like one
ので、少し短いものが付属していました
foot one foot cables these are I've got
フットワンフットケーブルこれらは私が持っている
a USB C and two USB micros yep so
USB Cと2つのUSBマイクロ
they're just nice little short cables
彼らはちょうどいい短いケーブルです
and I read your Apple connections ok so
そして、私はあなたのApple接続を読んで大丈夫です
it came with it so these are just like
それが付属していたので、これらはちょうどのようです
for your Android phones yeah and then
ええ、あなたのAndroid携帯電話用
these are for Apple so if you are using
これらはApple向けです。
this but if you are using this and all
これが、これとすべてを使用している場合
you have is Android 3 is not going to be
あなたはAndroid 3はそうではない
enough so you need to make sure that
十分なので、あなたはそれを確認する必要があります
you've got the right okay so when you
あなたは正しい大丈夫だから
buy this what do you do Jeff you buy
これを買うジェフを買う
some extra so we've got some nice color
余分なものがあるので、素敵な色があります
coated ones which my kids would
私の子供がコーティングするもの
absolutely love because then they'd be
絶対に愛するから
able to say well they've got the pink
彼らはピンクを持っていると言うことができます
one I've got the blue one and you know
私は青いものを持っているとあなたが知っている
solves everybody's problems based on the
に基づいて全員の問題を解決します
color coding perfect things you have to
あなたがしなければならない完璧なものを色分けする
do to like stop fights at home it's
家で戦いを止めるのが好きです
crazy oh those are nice oh yeah there's
クレイジーああそれらはいいですああそうそうあります
a very nice
とてもいい
or these do not come with it so you have
またはこれらは付属していないので
to buy separately so whatever works for
個別に購入するので、何でも機能します
you so we got three with it well two USB
あなたはそれで私たちはそれで3つを得ました
micro and one USB see yes and then we've
マイクロと1つのUSBはいを参照してください
got a bunch just to pack a sort of pack
ちょうどパックの種類をパックするための束を得た
here now everything they see is
ここに彼らが見るすべてがあります
available at cat5 TV slash charger
cat5 TVスラッシュ充電器で入手可能
you're right these are nice yeah those
あなたは正しいです、これらはいいです
these are like wound woven those nice
これらは素敵なそれらを編んだ傷のようなものです
cables but they're color-coded so the
ケーブルが色分けされているので
kids will love that all right so I have
子供たちは大丈夫だと思うので
unboxed okay really what we have is you
箱から出して大丈夫本当に私たちが持っているのはあなたです
have the base unit mm-hmm is there a
ベースユニットmm-hmmがあります
power cord I'll plug in the power cord
電源コード電源コードを差し込みます
while you're describing the power cord
電源コードを説明している間
you have the instructions that are just
あなただけの指示があります
not simple folow not a wall wart no just
単純なものではなく、壁のいぼではない
so you know okay so this is just gonna
だからあなたは大丈夫知っているので、これはちょうどつもりです
go right into your your outlet nicely
あなたのコンセントにぴったり入ります
and your plastic plexi dividers so these
プラスチック製のプレキシディバイダー
are like heavily sealed let's separate
厳重に密閉されているように分離しましょう
these puppies somehow I it's like air
これらの子犬はどういうわけか私は空気のようなものです
compressed oh they're vacuums yeah
圧縮されたああ、彼らはええ真空
vacuum sealed oh my god here we go this
ここで真空密閉されています
one well it's not vacuum sealed they're
一つは、それは彼らがいる真空密閉されていません
just a cycler on either side yeah okay
どちらかの側にサイクラーだけです
like you know someone feels vacuums this
あなたが知っているように誰かがこれを掃除機で感じる
has got power now jack Oh perfect okay
ジャックの電源がオンになりました
well I'm not gonna plug it in yet
まだプラグインするつもりはない
because I'm gonna be playing around with
遊んでるから
these but all right is there special way
これらは大丈夫です、特別な方法があります
these go in does not look oh yes there
これらは、そこに行くああそうではありません
is
は
okay so you can't really see it but
わかりましたので、あなたは本当にそれを見ることができませんが、
there's a little notches here which
ここには小さなノッチがあります
prevents you from putting this in
これを入れないようにする
backwards so if I do that it's not going
後方にあるので、そうすればそれは行かない
in because there's a little yeah yeah
なぜなら、そうそう少しあるから
nodules there then they go clicks then
そこに結節し、クリックしてから
perfect all right grab another one you
完璧な大丈夫もう一つをつかむ
want me to help I can help you do that
あなたがそうするのを手伝うことができます
all right
大丈夫
this takes three folks it's teamwork
これには3人が必要ですチームワークです
crazy how many invite some friends oh
なんて友達を招待してるの？
honey Chucky's does it take to put
ハニー・チャッキーは置くのに時間がかかる
dividers on a cell phone charging
携帯電話の充電器の仕切り
station thank you all right okay so we
駅は大丈夫だから大丈夫だから私たち
can get two phones in there look at this
そこに2台の電話を入れることができます
team action though much faster for this
チームアクションはこれに対してはるかに高速ですが
is the one I struggled with okay getting
私は大丈夫取得に苦労したものです
these suckers in there I feel like if
そこにこれらの吸盤私は
you're the person who changes the
あなたが変える人です
garbage at home and then you need to
ごみは家で
open the bag the new bag that's all
バッグを開ける新しいバッグがすべて
stuck together you know yes sir
一緒に立ち往生します
all right last ones going in okay here
最後に大丈夫です
we go all right USBC it has been
私たちは大丈夫ですUSBC
assembled
組み立てられた
okay so right away what I can see on it
大丈夫、すぐに私はそれで見ることができるもの
you have your physical switch button for
物理的なスイッチボタンがあります
power yeah your connectors are all on
電源がオンになっています
one side interestingly enough so the one
面白かったので
the unit I have at home
私が家に持っているユニット
the connectors are on either side so
コネクタは両側にあるので
I've got three and three Oh what I like
私は3つと3つ持っています
about that is it prevents all the cords
それについては、それはすべてのコードを防ぎます
from jumbling up on one side right this
片側にジャブリングすることから右これ
one they're all on one side so your
1つはすべて片側にあるため、
device is gonna have to sit because it's
それはだからデバイスは座っている必要があります
a short cable with the charging port
充電ポート付きの短いケーブル
going that way so depending on any case
どんな場合でもそうなるので
you have on your phone or any anything
携帯電話などで
like that it may cause problems but just
それは問題を引き起こすかもしれないが、ただ
for plugging it in oops
OOPSにプラグインするため
of course it's USB you got to do it a
もちろんそれはあなたがそれをするようになったUSBです
pretty different way that's right yeah
そうだね、かなり違う方法
yeah so but it just sticks in quite
ええそうですが、それはちょうど固執します
simply all right the one for there's
単に大丈夫です
pretty simple tech folks but yeah it
かなりシンプルな技術者ですが、そうです
really I did a USBC for my phone perfect
本当に完璧な携帯電話用のUSBCをしました
it's already connected to my phone
すでに私の電話に接続されています
because I thought hey we can actually
実際にできると思ったから
try like see then see if it explodes or
見るように試してから、爆発するか、
if it charges it's gonna do one of those
それが充電する場合、それらのいずれかを行うつもりです
two things yeah those are the only two
ええ、これらは2つだけです
options you're gonna learn one day the
いつか学ぶオプション
way to plug it in I know I haven't so
プラグインする方法
okay so that is plugged in via charge or
充電経由で差し込むか
the actual power cable connects here to
実際の電源ケーブルはここに接続します
the side I do like that it's just a
私が好きな側面はそれがただ
single power cord and then just a couple
単一の電源コード、そして数個
of yeah it is charging so I've powered
ええ、充電中なので電源を入れました
it on yeah you can see that no it was
ええ、あなたはそれがなかったことを見ることができます
off now it's on cuz the blue lights
オフになっています
kicked on Oh neat I don't know if you
きちんと蹴った
can see that yeah you guys see that a
ええ、皆さんはそれを見ることができます
little a right there I don't know if I
少し右そこに私はわからない
if I were to dim the lighting in the
私が照明を暗くするなら
studio here I don't know if you'd be
ここのスタジオ私はあなたがするかどうかわからない
able to see that a little bit better
それを少し良く見ることができます
maybe yeah yep that's good okay the blue
そうかもしれません
light now and when I turn it off I
今、光を消すと
noticed that it's only the blue light is
青い光だけが
only on on the one that the two that are
ある2つだけで
plugged in oh oh my god look at you you
プラグインされたああああ私の神はあなたを見て
observe and fella so yeah okay so you've
観察して、それで大丈夫です
got the power and then the one that it's
力を得て、それが
in plug in more that's it what happened
より多くのプラグインで、それは何が起こったかです
so let's log everything and to connect
すべてを記録して接続しましょう
sure connect
必ず接続する
I didn't get my phone what are you
私はあなたの電話を手に入れませんでした
looking for see ya I only have one see
屋を探している
all right you got to buy the right
大丈夫あなたは権利を買わなければなりません
cables folks but there's like a mine the
ケーブルの人々が、私のようなものがあります
one well I'm using it on my phone
よく私は私の電話でそれを使用しています
threaded once those are all see a USB
それらがすべてUSBになったらスレッド化
micro okay so you didn't get diversified
大丈夫だから、多様化することはなかった
pack okay yeah all right well let's test
パック大丈夫そう大丈夫テストしてみましょう
it this way if I move the connector to
このようにコネクタを移動すると
another port yeah cool look at that so
別のポートがかっこいいですね
you actually see the blue lights up
実際に青いライトが点灯します
Oh USB see as well yeah USB see sorry
ああUSBもそうそうUSBはごめんなさい
Sasha okay so in there it is charging
サーシャ大丈夫だから充電中です
this one has I believe built-in surge
これはビルトインサージを信じています
protection and stuff like that one of
保護とそのようなもの
the computers so it has built-in surge
コンピューターが組み込まれているので
protection it also has intelligent
また、インテリジェントな保護
charging with over voltage overcharge
過電圧過充電による充電
and overcurrent protection nice mine
そして、過電流保護素敵な鉱山
does not have that and truthfully when I
それを持っていないし、正直なところ私は
was looking for a banking station that
銀行の駅を探していました
wasn't something I was thinking of I
私が考えていたものではなかった
just wanted to be lucky to have all the
すべてを持っているだけで幸運になりたかった
phones outer parts yeah exactly so
電話の外側の部品はまさにそう
that's a nice very nice feature and it
それはとても素敵な機能であり、
is 10 and 50 watt total power what I
総電力は10ワットと50ワットです
don't see though is fast charge I don't
急速充電ですが、表示されません
see that either and it's a good comment
どちらかを参照してください、それは良いコメントです
because that's one of the questions
それは質問の一つだから
we're gonna get so ya know it looks like
私たちは手に入れようとしているので、
it's just straight like just regular
普通のようにまっすぐです
regular charge power yep now this
普通の充電電力
particular one now I'm sure those exist
特定の1つは今それらが存在することを確信しています
but I mean we're talking about charging
しかし、私たちは充電について話しているということです
six devices simultaneously which is
同時に6つのデバイス
pretty impressive
かなり印象的
it's pretty good from a single power I
単一のパワーからはかなり良い
also like the stability of this one Jeff
また、このジェフの安定性が好き
it's very solid doesn't move now one
とてもしっかりしているので動かない
thing I noticed about the one that I had
私が持っていたものについて気づいたこと
at home for the life mate I can't think
ライフメイトのために家では考えられない
of the model or the brand that it is
モデルまたはブランドの
there's an ally out there like tell
言うような味方がいる
there's tons yeah search for them but
それらのための検索ええトンがありますが、
what I wanted to check with yours is the
私があなたと確認したかったのは
gap between the placement spots so my
配置スポット間のギャップなので、私の
phone has a bit of a dip on the back
携帯電話の背面が少し落ち込んでいます
right where it yeah it is thicker and so
ええ、それは厚いです。
your phone sits quite nicely it's leaned
お使いの携帯電話はかなりきちんと座っています
back when I put mine in because of that
私がそのために私のものを入れたときに戻って
it sits up doesn't very much okay does
起き上がっても大丈夫ではない
that now I said matter
今、私は問題を言った
former bothers them well what it does
元はそれが何をするのかよく気にします
create a problem is if you if you're
もしあなたがあなたなら
trying to organize all your devices
すべてのデバイスを整理しよう
succinctly it doesn't work as well if
簡潔に言えば
one of them is falling forward it
それらの1つはそれを前方に落ちています。
bounces them all around especially
特に周りに跳ね返る
because I owed your phones when you put
あなたが置くときに私はあなたの電話を借りていたので
them in the charger no but for the one I
充電器に入れないで
have at home I have to do it in a
家で私はそれをしなければならない
certain order because of the different
異なるため、特定の順序
case sizes as one goes forward they all
ケースの大きさ
follow knocks them out so ok aware of
フォローはそれらをノックアウトするので
that like all these things you wouldn't
これらすべてのもののようにあなたはしないだろう
even think about exactly because of the
正確に考えて
the gap I mean that's that's finger
ギャップ私はそれが指だということです
width that's it so it's not like it's a
幅なので、それはそうではありません
big gap if you have a table at your
あなたのテーブルがある場合、大きなギャップ
tablet's gonna sit fairly pretty snug
タブレットはかなりぴったりと座る
yeah yeah so be aware of that but
ええそうだから、そのことに注意してください
otherwise that's it that's a nice little
それ以外の場合は、それは素敵な小さなです
okay the suckers small any guesses any
大丈夫吸盤は小さい
guesses iPod first-generation no ice
iPod第1世代の氷を推測します
crazy yeah doesn't even like when they
クレイジーそうだね
came with with like full touchscreen but
フルタッチスクリーンのように付属していますが、
that fits quite nicely but yeah I mean
それは非常にうまく収まりますが
if you have a tablet or something it's
タブレットなどをお持ちの場合は
going to sit a little bit higher and you
少し高く座って、あなたは
could see like mine is back on and
私が戻ってきたように見える
hanging that because that little knob is
その小さなノブが
not there but if you had a tablet with a
そこにはありませんが、タブレットを持っているなら
thicker case it's gonna sit straight up
厚い場合はまっすぐに座ります
there's no give and the chance with that
与えることもチャンスもありません
is if you accidentally bump it you could
誤ってぶつけた場合は
potentially break the plastic just
潜在的にプラスチックを破壊する
beware yeah well yeah I guess I mean
ええ、ええ、私は私が意味することを推測する
you're gonna find a safe place to put
あなたは置くための安全な場所を見つけるつもりです
this kind of parasite yeah plain and
この種の寄生虫は普通です
simple so but it keeps it in a
シンプルですが、それを保持します
centralized location and allows you you
集中管理された場所で
know especially if you have multiple
特に複数ある場合は知っている
devices at your home to organize
自宅のデバイスで整理する
everything you have all your phones
すべての携帯電話を持っているすべて
there you you know maybe you've got
そこにあなたは多分あなたが持っている知っています
young kids it's like get off the phone
若い子供たちは電話を降りるようなものです
that's your spot where you go this is
それはあなたが行くあなたのスポットですこれは
the phone charging sport yeah it's not
電話充電スポーツはそうではありません
in the rooms at night it's a central
夜の部屋でそれは中央です
location you know where every phone is
すべての電話がどこにあるかを知っている場所
and it's like this is kind of what I'm
そして、これは私がやっていることのようなものです
thinking like if if this works is a
これが機能するかどうかのように考える
great charger which it looks like it's
それはそれのように見える素晴らしい充電器
it's fantastic for this as a parent I'm
親としてこれが素晴らしい
gonna hide every other charger in the
他のすべての充電器を非表示にします
house yes and it's just here okay when
家はい、それはちょうどここに大丈夫です
your phone's dead put it on the charger
お使いの携帯電話の死者は充電器にそれを置きます
I know because I because we've updated
私たちが更新したので、私は知っています
to one of the you know something like
あなたのようなものに何かを知っている
this at home yeah I have so many wall
これは家でそう私は多くの壁を持っています
connectors now
今すぐコネクタ
like what am i doing me more raspberry
もっとラズベリーをやってるみたい
pi's that's exactly what yeah yeah so
パイはまさにそうそうそうです
yeah that's right nice job it comes up
ええ、それが出てくるのはまさにいい仕事です
one-year limited warranty which is kind
親切な1年間の限定保証
of nice normal wear and tear
普通のすり切れた
seals abuse misuse not cover damage
シールは損傷をカバーしない誤用を悪用します
trying to see if there's anything else
他に何かがあるかどうかを確認しよう
that's important to mention from the
それはから言及することが重要です
instructions I'm not seeing it mmm
表示されない指示mmm
I like that it has the surge protection
私はそれがサージ保護を持っていることが好きです
and everything else because your wall
あなたの壁だから
wart you're just how many times have you
いや、あなたは何回あなたがいる
just plug your phone into the wall well
電話を壁に差し込むだけ
exactly what happens if there's a power
力があれば正確に何が起こるか
surge or something
サージか何か
mm-hmm so that's kind of a bonus as well
mm-hmmこれも一種のボーナスです
yep nice so yeah that's it it is the G
うんうん、そうそうそれはそれがGです
chord six port 10 amp USB charging
コード6ポート10アンペアUSB充電
station specifically the black color
ステーション特に黒
there you go go to a cat5 dot TV slash
そこにcat5ドットTVスラッシュに行きます
charger if you're interested in that
興味があるなら充電器
particular one or of course follow that
特定の1つまたはもちろんそれに従う
link and then you can find various
リンクすると、さまざまなものを見つけることができます
alternatives as well Amazon's kind of
アマゾンの種類の代替品
cool that way you'll see some of the
そのようにクールなあなたはのいくつかを見るでしょう
other options that are similar but
同様ですが、他のオプション
different if you need quick charge then
急速充電が必要な場合は異なります
I guess that would be really the
それは本当に
deciding factor this one does feel like
これを決める要素は
it's really like quite sturdy yeah and I
本当に頑丈だよね
say that like it really does feel sturdy
本当に丈夫だと思う
you know really good I didn't even
あなたは本当に良いことを知っています
notice it's got like rubber grip pads in
ゴム製のグリップパッドのようになっていることに注意してください
there yeah I felt that when I put my so
そこにそうそう私は私がそう入れたときにそれを感じました
you know which is kind of nice holds the
どっちがいいかわかる
phone in place mm-hmm so that's okay
mm-hmmの場所に電話するので大丈夫です
well I will say in having used one of
よく私はのいずれかを使用したと言うでしょう
these now there's one thing that makes
これらは今、作るものが一つあります
me go you could take this to the next
これを持って行け
level that zapping feature
ザッピング機能のレベル
well the zapping feature would be
さて、ザッピング機能は
amazing cordless well court actually
実際に驚くべきコードレスウェルコート
cordless would be kind of cool if these
これらがあればコードレスはちょっとクールだ
had cordless charging plates but no yeah
コードレス充電プレートがありましたが
to allow one USB that a lot that does
多くのことを行う1つのUSBを許可する
data sync for a computer so all six
コンピューターのデータ同期なので、6つすべて
would be plugged in you plug it into
あなたはそれを差し込むでしょう
your computer and allow you want it to
お使いのコンピュータとあなたがそれをすることができます
be a hub as well how cool would that
ハブにもなります
Nora yes that would be a nice feature I
ノラはい、それはいい機能だろう
guess I think that's a whole new level
それは全く新しいレベルだと思う
yeah but then every phone would show up
ええ、しかし、すべての電話が表示されます
is it as a hard drive when you plug in
プラグインするときにハードドライブとして
your your charger no but think about
あなたの充電器いいえ、考えてみてください
nightly syncs like you got all your
あなたがすべてを手に入れたような毎晩の同期
family's phones hook up your family
家族の電話があなたの家族をつなぎます
phones yeah that would be a neat feature
ええ、それはすてきな機能になります
I guess I'll be kind of cool I don't
かっこいいと思うよ
know if any of the devices do it
デバイスのいずれかがそれを行うかどうかを知る
I mean now that I've used one of these
私はこれらのいずれかを使用したことを意味します
I'm like now would be a cool feature to
私は今にクールな機能になりそうだ
have yeah
ええ
next level yeah yeah you've gotta take a
次のレベルはいはい
really quick break folks when we come
私たちが来るとき、本当に速い休憩の人々
back I'm going to be showing you an app
戻るアプリを紹介します
that allows you to create app like
次のようなアプリを作成できます
browser windows on a modern Linux system
最新のLinuxシステムのブラウザーウィンドウ
stick around
くっつき回る
[Music]
[音楽]
these days we're surrounded by things
最近、私たちは物事に囲まれています
like Chromebooks Pyne book pros and and
Chromebooks Pyneブックのプロや
devices I mean the Chromebook is the
デバイスChromebookは
perfect example of a device that
そのデバイスの完璧な例
utilizes the Internet as an app
インターネットをアプリとして利用する
infrastructure right so I think about
インフラストラクチャが正しいので
things like like my Google Drive and
Googleドライブや
Google Docs and Google sheets and and
GoogleドキュメントとGoogleシート、および
and how those are very fast becoming my
そして、それらがどのように非常に速く私のようになっているか
applications for doing things like
のようなことをするためのアプリケーション
document editing mm-hmm
ドキュメント編集mm-hmm
I don't install Microsoft Office anymore
もうMicrosoft Officeをインストールしません
now right I use in my browser my Google
今すぐブラウザでGoogleを使用しています
Docs that's how I do it
それが私がそれをする方法であるドキュメント
you even Microsoft like word and all
マイクロソフトも言葉とすべてが好きです
that you can
あなたができること
they've got online database like Outlook
彼らはOutlookのようなオンラインデータベースを持っています
has gone into the cloud is like a
クラウドに入ったのは
browser-based thing but so these are all
ブラウザベースのものですが、これらはすべてです
things that they used to be applications
彼らがアプリケーションであったもの
on our computer and now they're
私たちのコンピューターで
progressively becoming more and more
徐々にますます
cloud driven and that means they are
クラウド主導型であり、
accessible through your web browser but
Webブラウザからアクセスできますが、
there's kind of like that old-school
そのような古い学校のようなものがあります
feel about having the native app on your
あなたのネイティブアプリを持つことについて感じます
computer having you know to do it in
あなたがそれを行うことを知っているコンピュータ
your web browser feels like you're going
あなたのウェブブラウザはあなたが行くように感じます
on a website to do it in the app feels
アプリでそれを行うためにウェブサイトで感じる
like you're opening a program and and
あなたがプログラムを開いているように、そして
and there's less screen real estate
そして、より少ない画面の不動産があります
that's wasted to things like the address
それはアドレスのようなものに無駄です
bar yeah yeah bookmarks and that kind of
bar yeah yeahブックマークなど
rhyme example QuickBooks Online perfect
韻の例QuickBooks Onlineパーフェクト
I use that for an organization that I'm
私は私がいる組織のためにそれを使用します
and it's funny because I have it
私はそれを持っているので、それは面白いです
installed on the computer yeah but then
ええ、コンピューターにインストールします
I can also login and and use it online
ログインしてオンラインで使用することもできます
on my personal computer looks exactly
私のパソコンでは正確に見えます
the same runs exactly this yeah but even
同じことがまさにそうですが、さらには
psychologically within my head I'm like
心理的に私の頭の中では
I would rather use the app right cuz
私はむしろ正しいアプリを使用したいです
that's the app it's a web browser and
それがウェブブラウザであるアプリです
you've got the address bar and
アドレスバーがあります
everything else so there have been
他のすべてがそうだったので
applications and and browsers themselves
アプリケーションとブラウザ自体
have things like app mode and and
アプリモードや
abilities to create a bit more of a
もう少し作成する能力
native feel to websites right so that
ウェブサイトに対するネイティブな感覚
they feel more like native apps but
ネイティブアプリのように感じますが、
there's it's it's never really been
本当にありませんでした
solidified as a standard so what rises
標準として固まったので、何が上がるか
up and then fizzles away like Firefox
Firefoxのように立ち上がって立ち消え
used to have a great mechanism for doing
行うための素晴らしいメカニズムを使用していた
this for creating an app kind of window
アプリの種類のウィンドウを作成するためのこれ
for your for your browser sessions but
あなたのブラウザセッションのために
it got discontinued so then it just
中止されたので
fizzled out but peppermint OS has done
ファズアウトしたが、ペパーミントOSは完了
something incredible with a tool that
そのツールで信じられない何か
they call ice and ice is so what they
彼らは氷と呼んでいます
call this is SSB which is a
これはSSBです
site-specific browser but the interface
サイト固有のブラウザですが、インターフェース
is really unique in that it it is
それはそれがであるという点で本当にユニークです
specifically it's not a web browser that
具体的には、それはウェブブラウザではありません
allows you to save an icon to your
アイコンを保存することができます
desktop that simply opens that website
そのウェブサイトを単に開くデスクトップ
every time you double-click on it no
ダブルクリックするたびに
it's it creates launchers on your Linux
Linuxにランチャーを作成するだけです
computer that look like the they look
彼らが見えるように見えるコンピュータ
like a native application it repairs all
ネイティブアプリケーションのようにすべてを修復します
of that browser stuff around the edges
その周辺のブラウザのものの
and everything else oh very cool but
他のすべては非常にクールですが、
they've made it very very simple but I'm
彼らはそれを非常にシンプルにしたが、私は
not using peppermint okay I'm actually
ペパーミントを使用していません
using Linux Mint and on Linux Mint which
Linux MintとLinux Mintを使用して
is a debian derivative it's also it's
debian派生物であり、それも
based on Ubuntu and this will go for
Ubuntuに基づいており、これはのために行きます
Ubuntu what what I want to show you is
Ubuntu私があなたに見せたいのは
for any Debian based distro so that's
Debianベースのディストリビューションの場合は、
Debian obviously we've been to
Debianは明らかに我々が行ったことがある
mint linux mint so i'm on linux mint 19
ミントLinuxミントだから私はLinuxミント19にいます
and it's it's fine for me to do those
そして、私がそれらをするのは大丈夫です
thing this on any of those distros okay
これらのディストリビューションのいずれかでこれを大丈夫
so i'm gonna jump into my web browser my
だから私は自分のウェブブラウザに飛び込むつもりだ
current one which is google chrome and
現在のgoogle chromeと
I'm gonna jump over to now observe this
これを観察するために飛び越します
URL that I'm gonna type in here
ここに入力するURL
peppermint OS dot-com slash guide slash
ペパーミントOSドットコムスラッシュガイドスラッシュ
ice and when I bring that up here we go
氷とそれをここに持ってきたら
an introduction to site specific
サイト固有の紹介
browsers they've got a great example
彼らは素晴らしい例を持っているブラウザ
there with Oh with the pixel editor
ピクセルエディターでああ
which is a web based image editor but by
これはWebベースの画像エディターですが、
using ice it looks like a native app on
アイスを使用すると、ネイティブアプリのように見えます
the computer really does how sweet is
コンピューターは本当に甘い
that the interface is stellar but
インターフェイスは恒星ですが、
because I'm not on peppermint OS it
私はペパーミントOSではないので
doesn't it's not available or come on my
それは利用できませんか、私の上に来ません
distro right
配布権
however peppermint OS is open source
ただし、ペパーミントOSはオープンソースです
right
正しい
it's debian based if you've got a debian
あなたがdebianを持っている場合、それはdebianベースです
based machine you're able to install the
あなたがインストールできるベースのマシン
things that they have open sourced and
彼らがオープンソース化したものと
compiled for their distro on my distro
私のディストリビューションで彼らのディストリビューション用にコンパイル
so here I am on Linux Mint let's see if
ここでLinux Mintを使用していますか
this is going to work for us so we're
これは私たちのために働くので、私たちは
gonna grab the source from not the
ではなくからソースを取得します
source but a binary packages from
ソースがバイナリパッケージから
Launchpad dotnet slash tilde peppermint
Launchpadドットネットスラッシュチルダペパーミント
OS / plus archive slash Lubuntu slash
OS /プラスアーカイブスラッシュLubuntuスラッシュ
ice - dev slash + packages and this
ice-devスラッシュ+パッケージとこれ
takes us to the packages folder for the
のパッケージフォルダーに移動します
ice development from the pepper mint OS
ペパーミントOSからの氷の開発
team and you see the latest version at
チームと最新のバージョンが表示されます
the time of this broadcast is version
この放送の時間はバージョンです
6.0 7.0 point 7 I should say so I'm
6.0 7.0 point 7私はそう言うべきです
gonna click on that and let's take a
それをクリックして、とりましょう
look at what we have here we've got
ここにあるものを見てください
packages and builds here's a build for
パッケージとビルドはこちらのビルドです
amd64 so because I am on a 64-bit Intel
amd64だから、私は64ビットIntelを使っているから
processor I'm okay to click on that and
プロセッサをクリックして大丈夫です
download the build theirs the Debian
Debianのビルドをダウンロードします
package
パッケージ
there and here it comes I'm gonna keep
そこに来て、私は続けるつもりです
that file and then I'm gonna click on it
そのファイルをクリックしてからクリックします
presumably dpkg is gonna try to launch
おそらくdpkgは起動しようとするでしょう
it and ask me what I want to do what is
それと私は何をしたいのか尋ねる
this web app integration for peppermint
ペパーミント用のこのWebアプリの統合
ice front end blah blah blah install
氷のフロントエンド何とか何とかインストール
package kind of love the way Linux makes
パッケージの種類はLinuxの好きな方法です
installers these days that's so much
最近のインストーラー
easier than the default where you used
使用したデフォルトよりも簡単
to have to log into terminal yeah
ええ、ターミナルにログインする必要があります
compiling from source I mean you can do
ソースからコンパイルすることができます
that so maybe you're not on AMD 64 and
それは多分あなたはAMD 64ではないでしょう
you need to compile all right so that's
コンパイルする必要があるので、
done what's changed close everything out
変更を加えてすべてを閉じます
nothing's changed so I'm gonna click on
何も変わっていないので、クリックします
here and I'm gonna type in ice and lo
ここで、私は氷とloを入力するつもりです
and behold there's an application now on
そして今、アプリケーションがあります
my computer called ice and just like
私のコンピューターはアイスと呼ばれ、
that I've got my simple what is it
私は私のシンプルなものを持っていること
called SSB is a site-specific browser
SSBと呼ばれるサイト固有のブラウザです
they call it a simple site-specific
彼らはそれを単純なサイト固有と呼びます
browser manager ok so it's this easy to
ブラウザマネージャーOK
create launchers and when I say a
ランチャーを作成し、私が言うとき
launcher I'm talking you know how
ランチャー私はあなたがどのように知っている話しています
onerous it can be to add things to like
面倒なことは、好きなものを追加することです
your internet category here let's say we
ここであなたのインターネットカテゴリは
want to turn YouTube into an app so
YouTubeをアプリに変えたい
let's call this YouTube and the URL is
これをYouTubeと呼びましょう。URLは
HTTP colon slash slash youtube.com and
HTTPコロンスラッシュスラッシュyoutube.comおよび
we're on the menu I'm actually not gonna
私たちは実際にメニューにありません
put it in Internet even though it's a
それがインターネットであっても
website I'm gonna put it in multimedia
ウェブサイトをマルチメディアに入れます
ooh wow what do I want the icon to look
うわー、私はアイコンに何を見せたいですか
like I'm gonna try this use site fav
私はこの使用サイトfavを試してみたい
icon I have yet to see that work it
iconまだ見たことがありません
doesn't seem to work so what I'm gonna
うまくいかないように思えるので
do instead is I'm going to click on my
代わりに、私をクリックします
browser and I'm going to type YouTube
ブラウザとYouTubeを入力します
icon I can jump into images I'm gonna
アイコン私はつもりの画像にジャンプすることができます
click on tools I'm going to click on
クリックするツールをクリックします
color I'm gonna choose transparent then
透明色を選択します
I'm gonna grab a transparent YouTube
透明なYouTubeを取得します
icon that doesn't have a background I'm
背景のないアイコンは
going to save that to my computer I'm
私のコンピューターに保存します
going to throw that into pictures I'm
それを私が写真に放り込む
going to make a folder called icons and
アイコンと呼ばれるフォルダを作成し、
save it there
そこに保存します
done now I have a file that quickly so
これですぐにファイルができました。
go into my home into where did I put it
私の家に入ってどこに置いたの
pictures where's pictures there it is
そこに写真がある写真
okay icons YouTube alright so now I've
大丈夫アイコンYouTube大丈夫だから今私は
chosen the YouTube icon there we go
YouTubeアイコンを選択しました
notice it will support chrome chromium
クロムクロムをサポートすることに注意してください
Vivaldi or Firefox so that's the back
VivaldiまたはFirefox
end it's going to use then it also so
終了しますそれから使用します
I'm gonna choose chrome because that's
それはだから私はクロムを選ぶつもりです
my browser okay it's detected that I
私のブラウザは大丈夫です
also have Firefox on here but I don't
ここにもFirefoxがありますが、私は
use it
これを使って
create an SSB with an isolated browser
分離されたブラウザでSSBを作成する
profile that means that within this app
このアプリ内で
if you will you are not going to it's
あなたがそれをするつもりがないなら
not going to share the session with your
あなたとセッションを共有するつもりはありません
real browser so I've logged into YouTube
実際のブラウザなので、YouTubeにログインしました
in Chrome if I don't have that checked
Chromeでチェックしていない場合
it will also it will be logged in in the
また、ログインされます
app so it's almost like an incognito
アプリなので、シークレットモードのようです
mode a sort of but it will no it's more
モードの一種ですが、それはそれ以上ではありません
like its own profile okay so you can log
独自のプロファイルが好きなので、ログに記録できます
into your youtube profile but it will
あなたのユーチューブのプロフィールに
only be logged in there so then similar
そこにログインするだけなので、同様の
so by contrast in chrome you will not be
したがって、クロムでは対照的に
logged in right okay clear you can
ログインして大丈夫
choose and and feel free to play with
選んで、気軽に遊んでください
that setting see what what way you want
その設定は、あなたが何を望むかを見る
it to be so I'm gonna say yes I want
そうだから、はい、私は欲しいと言うつもりです
this to be an isolated browser with
これは、独立したブラウザであり、
Chrome and I'm gonna go apply well again
クロムと私は再びうまく適用するつもりです
it doesn't seem to have done anything
何もしていないようです
but if I click on my Linux Mint menu and
しかし、Linux Mintメニューをクリックして、
I go into sound and video
私は音とビデオに入ります
I now see a button called YouTube no way
YouTubeというボタンが表示されるようになりました
that garnet these things let's uncheck
これらのガーネットはチェックを外しましょう
these things just because it does see
見ているからといってこれらのこと
because remember it's created a new
新しいものを作成したことを忘れないでください
profile right so I'm gonna say okay and
正しいプロファイルなので、私は大丈夫と言うつもりです
now I'm gonna close that just because
今からそれを閉じます
now that I've done that I want to show
見せたいことをやった今
you from scratch now that I've turned
あなたが最初からあなたが私が回ったので
off those things so sound in video
それらの事をオフにビデオで音
YouTube it's not gonna ask me those
YouTubeそれは私にそれらを尋ねるつもりはない
things again okay so YouTube is now its
再び大丈夫ですので、YouTubeは今
own window its own app it's it's going
独自のウィンドウ独自のアプリ、それは行くだろう
to behave very very much like an app but
非常にアプリのように振る舞いますが、
it's using Chrome as its background as
背景としてChromeを使用しています
its backend right so if you find that
バックエンドが正しいので、それを見つけたら
chrome performs better than Firefox
クロムはFirefoxよりも優れたパフォーマンスを発揮します
choose chrome if you find it's the
それが見つかった場合はクロムを選択してください
use firefox right if you want to remove
削除したい場合は、Firefoxを使用してください
one of those launchers from your menu so
あなたのメニューからそれらのランチャーの一つ
say I want to remove YouTube I can
YouTubeを削除したい
actually go to remove tab in ice
実際に氷のタブを削除するために行きます
highlight it and click on remove and
それを強調表示して[削除]をクリックし、
that will actually get it get rid of it
それは実際にそれを取り除くでしょう
you can do as many of these as you want
あなたはこれらのことを好きなだけ行うことができます
if you want to add like a category-5 TV
カテゴリ5のテレビのように追加する場合
let's say maybe you want to do the live
ライブをやりたいかもしれません
category 5 live so let's do that let's
カテゴリー5ライブ
go live cat 5 TV so then whenever and
ライブ猫5テレビに行くので、いつでも
you'll probably want our Icona if for
あなたはおそらく私たちのIconaが欲しいでしょう
the sake of the speed of tonight's
今夜の速度のために
demonstration I'm not going to do that
デモンストレーション私はそれをするつもりはありません
right now but you already saw how to do
今すぐですが、あなたはすでに方法を見て
that
それ
okay so category 5 live is under sound
大丈夫ですので、カテゴリ5のライブは正常です
and video there it is up there again
そしてそこにあるビデオは再びそこにあります
turn these things off oh I put like a
これらのことをオフにします
underscore or something but it's still
下線か何かですが、それでもまだです
working so so now I've got a launcher
だから今、私はランチャーを持っています
for category 5 when we're live so when
私たちが住んでいるときのカテゴリ5
we're live boom there we go
私たちはそこに住んでいます
Wow Inception right that's super super
うわー、それはすごい超
easy well is that so it is super super
とても簡単です
easy really quick works really well it's
簡単で本当に速い作品は本当にうまくいきます
effective and it's supported it's open
効果的でサポートされており、オープンです
source and it's available on any Debian
ソースおよびDebianで利用可能
distro that with a DB file it's already
DBファイルを使用したディストリビューション
compiled for amd64 and I think you'll
amd64用にコンパイルされており、
find other compiles there as well if you
もしあなたが他のコンパイルも見つけたら
dig through right so check that out it's
正しく掘り下げてください
called ice and from the folks who bring
氷と呼ばれ、もたらす人々から
us peppermint OS thank you very good
ペパーミントOSよろしくお願いします
thank you for that that's a great tool
それは素晴らしいツールだということをありがとう
great yeah another thing you may want to
あなたがしたいかもしれないもう一つのこと
add to your launchers is the category 5
ランチャーに追加するのはカテゴリ5です
TV news room yes yes yeah
テレビニュースルームはいはいはい
immediately in fact and now double click
実際にすぐにダブルクリックします
on it cuz it's time here's what's coming
その上に来ているのは時間だから
up in the category 5 TV newsroom
カテゴリ5のテレビニュースルーム
Microsoft no longer sees PlayStation
マイクロソフトはもはやプレイステーションを見ていません
maker Sony and Nintendo is the biggest
メーカーソニーと任天堂は最大です
competition for its Xbox pot
Xboxポットの競争
and you won't believe who they see as
そして、あなたは彼らが見ている人を信じません
their biggest threat an artist trick
彼らの最大の脅威はアーティストのトリック
Google into thinking that they were met
グーグルは彼らに会ったと思って
there were major traffic jams by pulling
引っ張ることによって主要な交通渋滞がありました
a wagon filled with smartphones down
スマートフォンでいっぱいのワゴン
empty streets arm is getting edgy with
空の通りの腕はとげのある取得しています
two new processor designs which bring
もたらす2つの新しいプロセッサ設計
swimline AI workloads to smart speakers
スイムラインAIワークロードをスマートスピーカーに
and other Internet of Things devices and
その他のモノのインターネットデバイス
windows trust an abandoned driver code
Windowsは放棄されたドライバーコードを信頼します
lets ransomware burrow deep into
ランサムウェアを深く潜らせる
targeted machine stick around the full
完全にターゲットマシンスティック
details are coming up later in the show
詳細はショーの後半で公開されます
this is the category 5.2 the newsroom
これはカテゴリー5.2のニュースルームです
covering the leak stop texting with a
漏れ止めテキストメッセージを
slight linux bias
わずかなLinuxバイアス
I'm Sasha Rickman joined this week by
今週参加したサーシャリックマンです
Jeff Weston and Robbie Ferguson some
ジェフ・ウェストンとロビー・ファーガソン
quick honourable mentions this week a
今週のクイック名誉言及
hacker crew managed to temporarily take
ハッカーの乗組員は一時的に取ることができた
control of Facebook's official Twitter
Facebookの公式Twitterの管理
account the irony in a tweet posted on
に投稿されたツイートで皮肉を説明する
February 7th at 3:50 p.m. on the
2月7日午後3時50分
official app Facebook Twitter feed the
公式アプリFacebook Twitterフィード
attacker posted hi we are our mine
攻撃者がこんにちは投稿しました
well even Facebook is hackable but at
Facebookでもハッキング可能ですが、
least their security better than Twitter
少なくともセキュリティはTwitterより優れている
they then went on to advertise their
その後、彼らは彼らの宣伝に行きました
services saying to contact them in order
順番に連絡するように言っているサービス
to quote improve your account security
アカウントのセキュリティを改善するための見積もり
unquote our mind did not say how they
私たちの心は彼らがどのように言っていない引用しないでください
got into the social networks Twitter
ソーシャルネットワークTwitterに入った
account but no self-respecting hacker
アカウントはあるが、自尊心のあるハッカーはいない
could would ever take pass up the
渡すことができます
opportunity to blast Facebook's security
Facebookのセキュリティを爆破する機会
practices according to a draft research
ドラフト調査による実践
paper from the astronomers who are
天文学者からの論文
analyzing it a mysterious radio signal
神秘的な無線信号を分析する
from space that was first detected in
で最初に検出されたスペースから
Canada appears to repeat at regular 16
カナダは定期的に16で繰り返されるようです
day intervals the you the unusual signal
日間隔あなたは珍しい信号
which has been traced back to a spiral
スパイラルまでさかのぼります
galaxy roughly 500 million light-years
約5億光年の銀河
from Earth is known as a fast radio
地球からの高速ラジオとして知られています
bursts aka FRB it has been fascinating
別名FRBのバースト
astronomers since Canada's chime
カナダのチャイム以来の天文学者
telescope first detected it in 2018
望遠鏡は2018年にそれを最初に検出しました
scientists have discovered hundreds of
科学者は何百ものを発見しました
seemingly random one-off FRBS over the
一見ランダムに見える一回限りのFRBS
last decade but only a handful of them
過去10年間だが、ほんの一握り
have been found to repeat now here's the
ここで繰り返すことが判明しました
thing this particular signal is not only
この特定の信号は
repeating but it appears to be sent out
繰り返しますが、送信されたように見えます
at regular intervals the signal starts
定期的に信号が始まります
and let me just say this is not sci-fi
これはSFではない
this is really reality the signal starts
これは本当に信号が始まる現実です
every sixteen point three five days it
16ポイントごとに3〜5日で
lasts four
4つ続く
or days and then fall silent for 12 days
または数日後に12日間沈黙する
before starting up again according to
に従って再起動する前に
the paper that is a recurring schedule
定期的なスケジュールである紙
the number of births within each four
各4人の出生数
day blast varied each time according to
デイブラストは
409 days worth of data that was compiled
409日分のデータがコンパイルされました
by chime the study authors say in their
チャイムによって、研究著者は彼らの中で言う
abstract quote our results suggest a
私たちの結果が示唆する抽象的な引用
mechanism for periodic modulation and
周期的な変調のメカニズム
disfavor
嫌い
models invoking purely sporadic
純粋に散発的なモデル
processes in other words and this is a
言い換えると、これは
not a quote so the quote is over but in
引用ではないので引用は終わりますが
other words the signal is not repeating
言い換えれば、信号が繰り返されていません
at random okay so they say that the
ランダムでいいので、彼らは言う
source may be flickering at regular
ソースが定期的にちらつくことがあります
intervals or some other factor might be
間隔またはその他の要因は
interrupting the signal blasts in a
で信号爆発を中断する
consistent pattern orbits come to mind
一貫したパターン軌道が頭に浮かぶ
for me like that could be part of it for
私にとっては、そのようなことができます
sure but if their findings are confirmed
確かですが、彼らの発見が確認された場合
the discovery would be another first in
発見は別の最初の
the early study of F R bees which have
持っているFRミツバチの初期の研究
only been known to science for a
科学的に知られているのは
relatively short period of time called
と呼ばれる比較的短い期間
the ultimate arm powered Nass Helios 64
究極のアーム駆動型Nass Helios 64
is accepting pre-orders discounted for
割引の予約注文を受け付けています
the first 500 Helios 64 is a full
最初の500 Helios 64はフル
fledged linux powered Nath solution that
本格的なLinuxベースのNathソリューション
offers built-in features that you will
組み込み機能を提供します
not find in any other product at this
これで他の製品で見つけられない
price point it supports up to 80
最大80までサポートする価格
terabytes of data storage in five hot
5つのホットでテラバイトのデータストレージ
swappable drive bays plus support for a
交換可能なドライブベイに加えて、
single m dot two for applications that
シングルmドット2
demand extra performance for
追加のパフォーマンスを要求する
connectivity it uses the new multi
新しいマルチを使用する接続性
gigabit speed standard on dual land
デュアルランドのギガビット速度標準
ports they offer up to 2.5 gigabits per
最大2.5ギガビット/ポートを提供するポート
second throughput the NASS uses an arm
NASSがアームを使用する2番目のスループット
64 hexa core SOC it features 4 gigabytes
4ギガバイトの64ヘキサコアSOC
of RAM and a 16 gigabyte EMM
RAMおよび16ギガバイトのEMM
for OS storage and booting now it's an
OSストレージと起動用になりました
ass that's basically behaving like a
お尻は基本的に
Linux computer so because the helio 64
Linuxコンピューターので、ヘリオ64
is open-source once it's released we're
リリースされるとオープンソースになります
going to begin seeing distributions
分布を見始める
created specifically for this hardware
このハードウェア専用に作成された
the Helios 64 was slated for release as
Helios 64は次のようにリリースされる予定です。
early as next month but with factory
早ければ来月ですが、工場で
shutdowns due to the corona virus the
コロナウイルスによるシャットダウン
first shipments will be delayed an ETA
最初の出荷はETAで遅延します
update will be provided by the company
更新は会社によって提供されます
once factory lines are allowed to reopen
工場ラインの再開が許可されると
in China but we estimate it to be late
中国では遅れていますが
spring or possibly early summer
春またはおそらく初夏
pre-orders are discounted to just are
先行予約は割引されます
you ready for this $285 to the first 500
最初の500に対して285ドルの準備ができました
orders and you can place that order now
注文すれば今すぐ注文できます
at COBOL dot io let's get into the top
COBOL dot ioでトップに入りましょう
stories we're following this week
今週フォローしているストーリー
Microsoft no longer sees PlayStation
マイクロソフトはもはやプレイステーションを見ていません
Maker Sony and Nintendo as the biggest
ソニーと任天堂が最大のメーカー
competition for its Xbox platform Phil
XboxプラットフォームPhilの競争
Spencer Microsoft's head of gaming said
スペンサーマイクロソフトのゲーミングヘッド
he now considered Amazon and Google as
彼は今、AmazonとGoogleを
his top rivals because of their cloud
彼らのクラウドのために彼のトップのライバル
computing infrastructure
コンピューティングインフラストラクチャ
he believes their transitional rivals
彼は彼らの過渡的なライバルを信じています
Nintendo and traditional rivals Nintendo
任天堂と伝統的なライバル任天堂
and Sony are out of step with the future
ソニーは未来と歩調を合わせていません
of gaming he said quote when you talk
あなたが話すときに彼は引用のゲームの
about Nintendo and Sony we have a ton of
任天堂とソニーについては
respect for them but we see Amazon and
それらを尊重しますが、アマゾンと
Google as the main competitors going
主要な競合他社としてのGoogle
forward that's not to disrespect
前方にそれは無礼ではない
Nintendo and Sony but the traditional
任天堂とソニーが伝統的な
gaming companies are somewhat out of
ゲーム会社はややアウト
position end quote
位置の終わりの引用
what cloud gaming players don't need to
クラウドゲーミングプレーヤーが必要としないもの
buy a games console instead the games
ゲームの代わりにゲーム機を購入する
are run on servers and huge data centers
サーバーと巨大なデータセンターで実行されている
with the footage streamed over the
映像が流れる
Internet to a TV computer smartphone or
インターネットからテレビコンピューターのスマートフォンまたは
a tablet
タブレット
it means players don't need to buy discs
プレーヤーがディスクを購入する必要がないことを意味します
or download games and software updates
またはゲームとソフトウェアの更新をダウンロードする
which can take a long time Google
Googleには時間がかかることがあります
entered the home gaming market in 2019
2019年に家庭用ゲーム市場に参入しました
with its stadia streaming service the
そのスタディアストリーミングサービスで
company's vast cloud computing business
会社の広大なクラウドコンピューティングビジネス
means that it has the necessary
それは必要があることを意味します
infrastructure in place but critics say
インフラは整備されているが、批評家は言う
the lineup of games on stadia stadia is
stadia stadiaのゲームのラインナップは
currently sparse while Amazon and Apple
現在はまばらで、AmazonとApple
offer games on their app stores and
アプリストアでゲームを提供し、
Apple offers a monthly subscription they
アップルは、彼らが毎月のサブスクリプションを提供しています
don't currently offer a cloud gaming
現在、クラウドゲームは提供していません
service however Amazon also operates an
ただし、Amazonは
enormous cloud computing business and is
巨大なクラウドコンピューティングビジネスであり、
rumored to be developing a game service
ゲームサービスを開発していると噂されている
Sony has offered its PlayStation now
ソニーは現在、PlayStationを提供しています
cloud gaming service since 2014
2014年以降のクラウドゲームサービス
letting gamers stream more than 700
ゲーマーに700以上のストリーミングを許可する
titles to a ps4 console or PC however it
PS4コンソールまたはPCのタイトル
currently streams games in 720p
現在、720pでゲームをストリーミングしています
resolution by contrast Google stadia can
対照的に、Google stadiaの解像度は
stream its games at up to 4k resolution
最大4kの解像度でゲームをストリーミング
NVIDIA has officially launched its
NVIDIAは正式に
GeForce now streaming service after
GeForceがサービスをストリーミングするようになりました
months of testing and both Sony and
数か月のテストとSonyと
Microsoft have already announced that
マイクロソフトはすでにそれを発表しています
they are still working on new games
彼らはまだ新しいゲームに取り組んでいます
consoles for home totally demonstrates
家庭用コンソールは完全に実証します
the shift
シフト
yeah and how things are being how
ええ、どのように物事がどのようになっている
technology is being provisioned I feel
テクノロジーがプロビジョニングされています
old I guess in the fact that my brain
昔の私の脳は
doesn't get it like I don't understa
私は理解できないようにそれを取得しません
locked into console mind-bending yeah
コンソールに圧倒されます
well we've been sold for so many years
私たちは何年も売られてきました
that the biggest most powerful console
最大の最も強力なコンソール
is going to give you the best gaming
最高のゲームをお届けします
experience now we're being told oh well
今の経験では、私たちはまあまあ言われています
you can do it on your phone you can do
あなたができるあなたの携帯電話でそれを行うことができます
it on this little $100 device you can do
あなたができるこの小さな100ドルのデバイスで
it on anything oh and then you can
なんでもかんでも
transition over to your computer which
お使いのコンピューターに移行します
doesn't even have to be a good computer
良いコンピューターである必要さえない
it can be a Chromebook yeah what I think
Chromebookでも構いません
the difference though and I mean
しかし違いは、私が意味する
admittedly I have not explored Google
確かに私はGoogleを探検していない
and Amazon gaming services so I can't
アマゾンのゲームサービスなので、私はできません
speak from first-hand knowledge but the
直接の知識から話すが、
ability to go offline is what separates
オフラインにする能力が別のものです
the two oh yeah yeah but but maybe
ああ、そうだね、でも多分
that's the ideas that were never offline
それは決してオフラインではなかったアイデアです
anymore well and sure we are but do we
もうよく、私たちは確かですが、私たちは
really but when we're at that point are
本当にですが、その時点では
it's just we're always connected Jeff
いつも私たちがつながれているだけ
but they're always connected business
しかし、彼らは常に接続されたビジネスです
you're right we are always connected but
あなたは正しいです、私たちは常に接続されていますが、
dives 860
ダイビング860
that's an assumption of necessary
それは必要だという仮定です
connectivity I like we see this with our
私が好きな接続性
kids all the time they play games that
子供たちはいつもゲームをします
are not online it's downloaded and
オンラインではなく、ダウンロードされている
that's it like sure minecraft is a great
それはMinecraftが素晴らしいことのようです
one for kids that are younger where
どこか若い子供向け
they're playing Minecraft it's not going
彼らはMinecraftをプレイしています
online I mean you could go to realms and
オンライン私はあなたが領域に行くことができることを意味し、
stuff but the difference here is yeah if
でも、ここの違いはそうです
you're gonna go with the cloud-based
あなたはクラウドベースで行くつもりです
computer gaming services you're stuck to
行き詰まっているコンピューターゲームサービス
a couple things you're stuck to what
あなたが何にこだわっているいくつかのこと
they offer from the choices and the
彼らは選択肢から提供し、
graphics and all that kind of stuff
グラフィックスなど
which I think again I don't know from
私は再び私が知らないと思う
first hand would be subpar compared to
最初の手は、
what you can pull out of say you know an
あなたが知っていると言うことから引き出すことができるもの
Xbox one ass or you know PlayStation 5
Xbox one assまたはPlayStation 5を知っている
with with their graphics I mean I can't
彼らのグラフィックで私はできないことを意味します
see playing like Red Dead Redemption 2
Red Dead Redemption 2のようなプレイをご覧ください
on my phone
自分の携帯電話に
you can't you still it's from a
あなたはまだできません
technological perspective everything's
技術的な視点すべてのもの
going cloud yes but the the quality so
はい、クラウドに行きます
you're saying will it look as good so
あなたはそれが同じように見えるだろうと言っている
the quality is not the video the video
品質はビデオではありませんビデオ
is your my TV is 1080p so it's 1920 by
あなたのテレビは1080pなので、1920年です
1080p regardless of how powerful my
どれだけ強力であっても、1080p
system is or not so yet for some reason
何らかの理由でシステムがまだそうであるかどうか
if I use a first gen we versus a
第一世代を使用する場合、
Playstation 4 I'm going to notice a
プレイステーション4私は気づくつもりです
quality difference in the pricing and
価格設定の品質の違い
ensure it's a different system and so it
別のシステムであることを確認してください
is apples to oranges but what I mean is
リンゴとオレンジですが、私が言いたいのは
the power of that more powerful system
そのより強力なシステムの力
even though my TV never changed
私のテレビは変わらなかったのに
resolution it's still the same
解像度は同じです
resolution the video quality is still
ビデオ品質はまだ解像度
the same right ok but it looks so much
同じ権利は大丈夫ですが、それはとても見えます
better because that one is so much more
そのほうがずっといいから
powerful so now take that and put it
強力なので今それを取り、それを置く
into a cloud server where this cloud
このクラウドのクラウドサーバーに
server is still streaming 1920 by 1080 P
サーバーはまだ1920 x 1080 Pをストリーミングしています
2 to my 1080p TV mhm and yet it has so
私の1080p TV mhmに2つ、それでもそうです
much power yes it's a
多くの力はい、それは
multibillion-dollar system
数十億ドルのシステム
versus my little $400 right console
私の小さな400ドルの適切なコンソールに対して
right so so the the the resolution is
そうですので、解像度は
not the bottleneck now our our Internet
ボトルネックではなく、インターネット
is capable of streaming 4k video in real
実際に4kビデオをストリーミング可能
time with no latency right that's
待ち時間のない時間です
incredible
信じられない
mm-hmm so now put it back and in there
mm-hmmだから今それをそこに入れて
that is so powerful that I can do that
それは私ができるほど強力です
on my cheap device yeah and on any
私の安いデバイスで
device and I can transition from device
デバイスとデバイスから移行できます
to device I don't have to buy anything
デバイスに私は何も買う必要はありません
in particular to be able to use my games
特に私のゲームを使用できるように
and the transition is happening but the
そして、移行が起こっていますが、
transitions going to be difficult for
移行が困難になる
people like me who still like to go to
まだ行きたいと思う私のような人々
the store and buy a game and you and I
ストアとゲームを購入し、あなたと私
actually kind of and if the business you
実際にビジネスの場合
take it with you and put it on and I
あなたとそれを取り、それを置くと私
hesitate even buying digital copies of
のデジタルコピーの購入もためらう
games like I like to have the actual
私が実際に持っているようなゲーム
game but I understand that the future is
ゲームですが、私は未来が
is coming up quick I'm still gonna buy a
すぐに来ます私はまだ買うつもりです
PS 5 right I'm gonna also likely play
PS 5右私もプレイするつもりです
games on stadia right yeah and that's
スタジアムでのゲームはまさにそうです
that's an interesting point I want to
それは私がしたい興味深い点です
just reiterate what you just said which
ちょうどあなたが言ったことを繰り返します
is I'm going to also play videos on
私もビデオを再生するつもりです
stadia stadia so I don't think that
スタディアスタディアだとは思わない
we're replacing that offline phone
オフラインの電話を交換しています
device I think we're supplementing it
デバイス私たちはそれを補足していると思う
and say it enhance hey now okay you can
そして、それはちょっと大丈夫あなたができる大丈夫だと言います
you can also when you're connected to
あなたがに接続しているときにもできます
the internet play games that you can't
あなたができないインターネットプレイゲーム
play when you're offline that are like
オフラインのときにプレイする
high-end
ハイエンド
yeah and that's where okay maybe this is
ええ、それは大丈夫です多分これは
just another another platform and we all
別の別のプラットフォームと私たち全員
have multiple plans that's right yeah I
ええ、私は複数の計画を持っています
wonder if they'll have it like now
彼らは今のように持っているのだろうか
here's the latency is too high for VR
遅延がVRには大きすぎる
here's an eye we have got to be able
ここに私たちができるようになった目があります
it's gotta be able to track you with
それを使ってあなたを追跡することができなければなりません
this right now so I mean like you've
これが今だから
brought up VR which you know totally
あなたが完全に知っているVRを育てました
make sense yes what about things like
理にかなっています
framerate
フレームレート
because you said 64k that's pretty good
あなたは64kと言ったので、それはかなり良いです
to me yeah I hear you but you're talking
私にはうん、あなたの声は聞こえるがあなたは話している
about the screen resolution I mean if
画面の解像度について
your internet can't keep up it's gonna
あなたのインターネットはそれを維持することができません
impact your gameplay do you remember
ゲームプレイに影響を与えますか
when we used to be like oh I'm like I'm
私たちがかつてのようだったとき、私は私が
so bad yeah like in order to go back to
とても悪いええに戻るために
lagging or my car my kids gonna go yes
遅れているか私の車は私の子供がはい行くつもりです
however consider this as and I know we
しかし、これを考慮し、私たちは知っています
do need to move on to the next story but
次の話に進む必要がありますが
consider that the very companies that
まさにその企業が
are pushing the technology shift are the
技術シフトを推進しています
same companies who are controlling the
を制御している同じ会社
introduction of like Google's gigabit
Googleのようなギガビットの導入
fiber to the home right right so yeah if
家庭へのファイバー
that's the case oh you know it's gonna
それはそうだね
perform well it's like you you you just
上手くやる
know that that's what they're driving
それが彼らが運転しているものであることを知っています
toward and and they're not gonna build a
に向けて、彼らは構築するつもりはありません
service that's gonna fail based on that
それに基づいて失敗するサービス
this latency is a big thing sure sure
このレイテンシは確かに大きなものです
because this is internet-based
これはインターネットベースであるため
it's going to be it's going to resolve
それは解決するだろう
the cross-platform compatibility issues
クロスプラットフォームの互換性の問題
it's an interesting thing though because
でも面白いことです
you have to remember that this is not
これはそうではないことを覚えておく必要があります
game streaming this is video streaming
ゲームストリーミングこれはビデオストリーミングです
we've already proven through YouTube and
YouTubeで既に証明済みで、
through everything else that video
そのビデオの他のすべてを通して
streaming is great these days yep
ストリーミングは最近素晴らしい
there's no latency on videos like like
次のような動画には待ち時間がありません
really in real time if it was real time
リアルタイムなら本当にリアルタイムで
so they've created real time video
リアルタイムのビデオを作成しました
streaming service that has the
ストリーミングサービス
interactivity of controls and control
コントロールとコントロールの相互作用
doesn't take a lot of bandwidth no so
帯域幅をあまり必要としません
it's like it's instant as long as you
それはあなたがいる限りそれが瞬時であるようなものです
don't have high pings
高いpingはありません
right as long as you don't have latency
待ち時間がない限り
on your internet connection and that's
あなたのインターネット接続で、それは
the key thing and so they'll be driving
重要なことなので、彼らは運転します
ISPs to support their codecs and you'll
ISPがコーデックをサポートすると、あなたは
see an evolution in that kind of thing
そのようなことの進化を見る
very cool if you've tried stadia or any
スタディアなどを試してみたらとてもクール
other cloud-based service comment below
以下の他のクラウドベースのサービスのコメント
let us know if you've been contemplating
あなたが考えているなら教えてください
it maybe post why you haven't tried it
試したことがなかった理由を投稿するかもしれません
you know what's holding you up artist
何がアーティストを支えているのか知っている
Simon wacker noticed something unusual
サイモン・ワッカーは珍しいことに気づいた
at a made a demonstration in Berlin
ベルリンで行われたデモで
Google Maps showed that there was a
Googleマップでは、
massive traffic jam even though there
大規模な渋滞があったとしても
were zero cars on the road soon enough
すぐに道路に車がなかった
wicked realize that it was the mass of
邪悪なのは、それが
people or
人または
specifically their smartphones that had
特に持っていた彼らのスマートフォン
inadvertently tricked Google into seeing
誤ってGoogleをGoogleして見させた
gridlock on an empty street and then he
空の路上で渋滞し、彼は
decided to do it himself where Kurt says
カートが言うところ、自分でやることに決めた
quote the question was if it might be
質問を引用してください
possible to generate something like this
このようなものを生成することが可能
in a much simpler way I don't need the
もっと簡単な方法で私は必要ありません
people I just need their smart phones
スマートフォンが必要な人
end quote
引用終了
so he borrowed phones from friends and
彼は友人から電話を借りて
rental companies until he had acquired
彼が買収するまでレンタル会社
99 devices which he piled into a little
彼が少し積み上げた99個のデバイス
red wagon the plan was simple over the
赤いワゴンは計画がシンプルだった
course of a day a worker would walk up
ある日、労働者が歩いて行く
and down a given Street mostly at random
そして、ほとんどランダムに与えられた通りを下る
towing his smartphone packed wagon
スマートフォンを詰めたワゴンをけん引
behind him the effect wasn't
彼の後ろに効果はなかった
instantaneous it took Google Maps about
Google Mapsにかかった瞬間
an hour to catch up but eventually
追いつくまで1時間
inevitably record said that his wagon
必然的に記録は彼のワゴンと言った
would create a huge long red line in the
で巨大な長い赤い線を作成します
app indicating that a traffic had slowed
トラフィックが遅くなったことを示すアプリ
to a crawl even though there wasn't any
クロールはありませんでしたが
traffic at all he had effectively
彼が持っていたすべてのトラフィック
tricked the system into thinking a
システムをだまして考えさせた
series of large buses was crawling back
大型バスのシリーズがクロールバックしていました
and forth Google said in a statement
グーグルは声明で言った
quote traffic data in Google Maps is
Googleマップでの交通量データの引用は
refreshed continuously thanks to
おかげで継続的に更新
information from a variety of sources
さまざまなソースからの情報
including aggregated and anonymized the
集約および匿名化を含む
data from people who have location
位置情報を持っている人からのデータ
services turned on and contributions
オンになっているサービスと貢献
from the Google Maps community end quote
Googleマップコミュニティからの引用
they note that while it had figured out
彼らはそれがわかったが
how to distinguish between cars and
車を区別する方法と
motorcycles it does not yet have any way
オートバイはまだ方法がありません
to filter for a wecord set up Weikart
Wecordセットアップ用にフィルタリングするWeikart
says quote what I'm really interested in
私が本当に興味を持っていることを引用する
generally is the connection between
一般的には
technology and society and the impact of
技術と社会との影響
technology how it shapes us end quote
テクノロジーどのように形作られるか
the hack is getting attention not only
ハックは注目されているだけではありません
because it's fun but also serves as a
楽しいだけでなく、
necessary reminder that the system's
システムの
people take for granted involve inputs
人々は当然のこととしてインプットを含む
and outputs and that they themselves are
そして出力と、それ自体が
sometimes both it shows how simple it is
時には両方がそれがいかに簡単かを示します
to be it's how simple it is to fool a
であるためにそれはそれがいかに簡単であるか
product in which people place a trim
人々がトリムを配置する製品
Bendis amounts of trust how this
ベンディスはこれをどのように信頼しているか
interesting there's a lot of fun but I
おもしろいことがたくさんありますが、私は
love how the artist has found the spin
アーティストがスピンを見つけた方法が大好き
to say hey maybe we're trusting the
多分私たちは信頼していると言って
technology a little too much that yeah
テクノロジーが少し多すぎる
so much so that anyone looking at their
そんなに見ている人は誰でも
app or using their GPS that's powered by
アプリまたは電源を使用しているGPSの使用
Google services yes is avoiding those
Googleサービスは、それらを避けています
areas based on his little experiment
彼の小さな実験に基づいた領域
right so when when I had first heard
そうだから私が最初に聞いたとき
this story I thought to myself okay so
私は自分自身に大丈夫だと思ったこの物語
four people are in a car like if you're
あなたがいる場合のように4人が車にいます
carpooling and you're stuck in a slow
相乗りとあなたは遅いで立ち往生しています
section of the highway is it gonna show
高速道路のセクションが表示されます
up way busier on the highway than it
それよりも高速道路で忙しい
actually is it's completely yeah I I
実際にそれは完全にそうですII
personally use Waze which is owned by
個人所有のWazeを使用します
Google it it's yeah it's I think it's
グーグルそれはええそれはだと思う
the exact same well no there's some
まったく同じですいくつかあります
enhanced features that Google Maps
Google Mapsの拡張機能
doesn't he'll differently yeah but what
彼は違うええではないでしょうが
I like about Waze is is that it is user
Wazeが好きなのは、ユーザーであることです
input unlike a lot of Google Maps that
多くのGoogleマップとは異なり、入力
is drawn by anonymous unit user data and
匿名ユニットのユーザーデータによって描画され、
things happening in the backend so ways
バックエンドで起こっていることなので、
builds off Google Maps but then you can
Googleマップを構築しますが、次のことができます
add your individual components into it
個々のコンポーネントを追加します
but I have at times how to phone call or
しかし、私は時々電話をかける方法や
text or something come in where it's
テキストや何かがそこにある
like I need to respond to this so I'll
これに応答する必要があるように
pull over on the side of the road do the
道路の脇に引っ張ります
thing that I need to do and all sudden I
私がする必要があることと、すべて突然
get an alert on my phone we're detecting
検出している電話でアラートを取得する
a slowdown oh you know are you in
あなたはあなたが知っている減速ああ
traffic how heavy is the traffic and I'm
トラフィックはどれくらい重いですか？
like pulled over and so I'll say no and
引っ張られたようなので、私はノーと言います
move on this is this is odd Jeff is not
これに移動しますこれは奇妙ですジェフはそうではありません
texting while driving this is character
これを運転中のテキストメッセージはキャラクターです
for you but what what I could have done
あなたのために
is gone
なくなっている
yes heavy traffic sure traffic's flowing
はい渋滞は確実に流れている
beside me well so I mean if there is
私のそばにいるので
that user element so I've never fully
そのユーザー要素なので、私は完全に
trusted the information I see on those
私がそれらで見る情報を信頼した
services because I know that there is
サービスがあることを知っているので
that user input data right actually
ユーザーが実際にデータを入力した
today on my way to the studio I always
今日スタジオに行く途中でいつも
use Google Maps I even though I know how
Googleマップを使用する
to get here I always use it I like I
ここに来るために私はいつもそれを使用します
like to be told what to do but Google
何をすべきか言われるのが好きですが、Google
told me to take the highway and I looked
高速道路を取るように言われた
at the highway and I thought ah that's a
高速道路で、私はああだと思った
dead stop
行き止まり
and Google was pretty mad at me like it
そして、Googleはそれが好きで私にかなり怒っていました
kept trying to correct me back to the
に私を修正しようとし続けた
highway but I was like I am taking the
高速道路が、私は取っているようだった
main road was it just that one spot and
主要な道はただその1つの場所であり、
then it was fine after yeah there's one
それはそうだった後、それは大丈夫だった
spot on the highway right now
今、高速道路にスポット
okay so this this opens up something
さて、これは何かを開く
though interesting about and I know we
面白いけど私たちは知っている
need to move to the next story but about
次の話に移る必要があります
proximity how specific is location-based
近接度特定の場所ベースの方法
services on the phone because like my
私のようなので、電話でのサービス
kids play pokemon go yeah so when
子供たちはポケモンをプレイします
they're at home if they move from one
彼らは1から移動する場合、彼らは家にいます
side of the living room to the next
隣の居間の
their character moves with them yeah but
キャラクターは一緒に動きます
when I'm sitting in the car I'm getting
車に座っているときは
a bigger blip on the map and so I don't
地図上に大きなブリップがあるので、私はしません
know if it can update as quick to my
それは私のように迅速に更新できるかどうかを知っています
precise location it's probably lulling
おそらく落ち着いている正確な場所
you into a false sense of like anonymity
あなたは匿名のような誤った感覚にあなたを
it knows exactly where you it know
あなたが知っている場所を正確に知っています
exactly where you're parked so then
まさにあなたが駐車している場所
Google have not built something into the
Googleは何かを組み込みませんでした
programming that it watches for the
監視するプログラミング
collection of devices and it goes there
デバイスのコレクションとそれはそこに行きます
are 99 within this box that's not actual
このボックス内の99は実際ではありません
I think they will know okay we have got
私たちが持っている大丈夫知っていると思う
to take a quick break more of this
これをもっと簡単に
week's top tech stories are coming up
今週のトップテクノロジーストーリーが登場します
don't go anywhere
どこにも行かないで
[Music]
[音楽]
welcome back urn has announced the Evo's
ウェルカムバックurnはEvoを発表しました
view 55 and the cortex-m 55 for edge
ビュー55およびエッジのcortex-m 55
devices bringing an AI neural network
AIニューラルネットワークをもたらすデバイス
accelerator to futures smart speakers
先物スマートスピーカーへのアクセラレータ
light bulbs fridges and other IOT
電球冷蔵庫およびその他のIOT
devices the more powerful of the two
2つのデバイスのうち、より強力なもの
known as the cortex-m 55 is a general
cortex-m 55として知られているのは一般的な
microcontroller grade cpu blueprint well
マイクロコントローラグレードのCPU設計図
the other names ethos yu55 is
他の名前はethos yu55です
essentially an AI accelerator the
本質的にAIアクセラレータ
cortex-m 55 is based on arms helium
cortex-m 55は腕のヘリウムに基づいています
technology the ethos u 55 on the other
テクノロジーethos u 55
hand is a novel architecture forearm and
手は斬新な建築の前腕であり、
has been described as a micro neural
マイクロニューラルとして記述されています
processing unit or micro NPU for short
処理装置または略してマイクロNPU
both processors are available now to
両方のプロセッサが現在利用可能です
license and are intended to be used
ライセンスされ、使用されることを意図している
together the m55 running application
一緒にm55実行中のアプリケーション
code the u55 doing all the neural
すべてのニューラルを行うu55をコーディングする
network mathematics in fast Hardware the
高速ハードウェアのネットワーク数学
senior director of the IOT and embedded
IOTのシニアディレクターおよび組み込み
team at arm says quote the micro NPU
腕のチームは、マイクロNPUを引用すると言います
cannot be used on its own it needs to be
単独で使用することはできません
paired with a CPU like the cortex m55
cortex m55などのCPUとペアになっている
together the system delivers 480 times
一緒にシステムは480回を提供します
the performance compared to previous
以前と比較したパフォーマンス
cortex-m generations working on their
に取り組んでいる皮質-m世代
own end quote
自身の終了の引用
we expect to see chips using these
私たちはこれらを使用したチップを見ることを期待しています
blueprints early next year
来年初めの青写真
awesome I can't believe this is real
これは本物だとは信じられない
life but neural processing units are now
生命ですが、神経処理ユニットは今
I know heart of an SOC like this is so
私はこのようなSOCの心を知っています
it's just signed by to my what exactly
それはちょうど私のものに署名されています
an eighties mind like I remember when
私が覚えているような80年代の心
which Star Trek was it where they use
スタートレックはどこで使用したか
the neuro packs what are they called
ニューロパックは何と呼ばれていますか
oh my gosh one of the Star Trek's was an
ああ、スタートレックの1つは
enterprise maybe where there's like Oh
ああみたいなところかもしれない企業
to have like telepresence yeah within
テレプレゼンスのように
the ship and like they would blow out
船と彼らが吹き消すような
and they'd have to replace
そして、彼らは交換する必要があります
them and they're like these gel pack
それらは、これらのゲルパックのようなものです
things and I'm like that would never
物事と私はそれは決してないだろうようだ
happen I think it was Star Trek I
たまたまスタートレックだと思う
understand that what I remember watching
私が見たことを覚えていることを理解する
that I think I'm Star Trek Enterprise
スタートレックエンタープライズだと思う
and I was like there's no way we're
そして、私たちがいる方法はないようなものでした
gonna have that kind of advanced
そのような高度を持っているつもり
technology it's not possible this is
これは不可能な技術です
like 15 20 years ago and now I'm
20年前の15のように、今私は
watching stuff like this coming where
このようなものを見てどこに来る
it's like neuro networks I'm like oh my
神経回路網のようなものです
goodness
良さ
every year there's a new possibility and
毎年新しい可能性があり、
I never would have expected this this is
これは予想していなかったでしょう
yeah yeah like so we're talking like the
ええええので、私たちはのように話している
next gen of yes AI which is so crazy
次世代のはいAIはとてもクレイジーです
that these little chips can now process
これらの小さなチップが処理できるようになりました
teraflops worth of information like it's
テラフロップス相当の情報
I don't know what it really is but it's
それが本当に何なのかわかりませんが、
like ridiculous amounts of data having
とんでもない量のデータが
to do with AI right so that so the next
AIを正しく行うために、次のように
thing is that the you know coders will
ことは、あなたがコーダーが知っているということです
be able to make thinking devices so
思考装置を作ることができるように
those smart speakers with this and with
これとこれらのスマートスピーカー
this technology will be smarter the fact
この技術は事実より賢くなるでしょう
that there are two separate things like
のような2つの別々のものがあること
I'm surprised that well you have to have
私はあなたが持っている必要があることに驚いています
a CPU you have to have the ability to
あなたがする能力を持っている必要があるCPU
run traditional code yeah otherwise you
そうでなければ伝統的なコードを実行します
wouldn't be able to like you wouldn't be
あなたが好きではないことを好きになることはできません
able to as a human interact with it
人間としてそれと対話することができる
there has to be a layer for humans to be
人間が存在するためのレイヤーが必要です
able to access the NPU yeah hmm
NPUにアクセスできます
otherwise it just blow our minds how
それ以外の場合は、どのように私たちの心を爆破する
quickly before this would be adapted for
これが適応される前にすぐに
phones and Technology in phones right
電話と電話の技術
but I mean at this level
でもこのレベルでは
I don't know like because that could
それができるから
change mobile computing sure it's gonna
モバイルコンピューティングを変更する
change a lot of sauce but the idea is
ソースをたくさん変えますが、アイデアは
that it's getting faster smaller yeah
速くなっているということですね
and more integrated that's the way
より統合された方法です
technology goes and so we're seeing a
テクノロジーが進むので、
massive shift in how data is processed
データの処理方法の大幅な変更
because we're specifically looking
特に探しているからです
toward AI not far in machine learning
機械学習でそれほど遠くないAIに向けて
Arvest they're little pluses attackers
彼らは攻撃者に少しプラスだと思う
behind one of the world's most more
世界で最も多くの
destructive pieces of ransomware have
ランサムウェアの破壊的な部分には
found a new way to defeat defenses that
防御を打ち破る新しい方法を見つけました
that might otherwise prevent the attack
そうでなければ、攻撃を防ぐことができます
from Incred encrypting data installing a
Incred暗号化データのインストールから
buggy driver first and then hacking it
バギードライバーが最初にハッキングする
to burrow deeper into the targeted
ターゲットをより深く掘り下げる
computer the ransomware in this case is
この場合のランサムウェアは
Robin Hood known for taking down the
降ろすことで知られるロビン・フッド
city of Baltimore networks and systems
ボルチモア市のネットワークとシステム
in Greenville North Carolina Robin Hood
グリーンビルノースカロライナロビンフッド
can easily encrypt sensitive files once
機密ファイルを一度簡単に暗号化できます
a vulnerability has allowed the malware
脆弱性がマルウェアを許可しました
to gain a toehold
つま先を得る
for networks that are better fortified
より強化されたネットワーク向け
the ransomware ax has a harder time
ランサムウェアのxは苦労しています
breaking in now Robin Hood has found a
今ロビンフッドに侵入は発見しました
way to defeat these defenses in two
これらの防御を2つで打ち負かす方法
recent attacks researchers from security
セキュリティからの最近の攻撃研究者
firm Sophos said the ransomware has used
ソフォスは、ランサムウェアが
its access to a targeted machine to
対象マシンへのアクセス
install a driver from taiwan-based
台湾ベースのドライバーをインストールする
motherboard manufacturer gigabyte that
マザーボードメーカーギガバイト
has a known vulnerability in it it's the
既知の脆弱性があります
same vulnerability that led to gigabyte
ギガバイトにつながった同じ脆弱性
officials discontinuing the use of the
職員の使用を中止
driver but since it contains gigabytes
ドライバーがギガバイトを含むため
cryptographic signature the Windows
Windowsの暗号署名
operating system trusts it and allows it
オペレーティングシステムはそれを信頼し、許可します
it allows it to run in the highly
それは非常に実行することができます
sensitive Windows kernel region of the
の敏感なWindowsカーネル領域
OS without question whisks a benign but
疑いのないOSは良性ですが、
buggy driver installed Robin Hood then
その後、バギードライバーがRobin Hoodをインストールしました
exploited the vulnerability to gain the
脆弱性を悪用して
ability to read and write to virtually
仮想的に読み書きする能力
any memory region chosen by the attacker
攻撃者が選択したメモリ領域
the Robin Hood exploit changed a single
ロビン・フッドのエクスプロイトは単一の
bite to disable the windows requirement
噛んでWindowsの要件を無効にします
that drivers be signed
ドライバーに署名する
with that Robin Hood installed its own
ロビン・フッドが独自にインストールした
unsigned driver that used its highly
高度に使用した無署名のドライバー
privileged kernel access to kill
killする特権カーネルアクセス
processes and files belonging to
に属するプロセスとファイル
endpoint security products the advanced
エンドポイントセキュリティ製品
status of the driver gave it greater
ドライバーのステータスはそれを大きくしました
ability than other techniques to ensure
保証する他の技術よりも能力
that the targeted processes are
対象プロセスは
permanently stopped there are other
永久に停止した他の
windows trusted drivers with known
既知のWindows信頼できるドライバー
vulnerabilities that could be used in
で使用される可能性のある脆弱性
the same way of gigabytes drivers these
これらのギガバイトドライバーの同じ方法
include sign drivers from VirtualBox
VirtualBoxのサインドライバーを含める
novel cpu-z and asus and while the
小説cpu-zとasusおよび
gigabyte driver may be the first known
ギガバイトのドライバーは最初に知られているかもしれません
instance of this type of hack it is it
このタイプのハックのインスタンスはそれです
very well may not be the last and points
非常によく最後とポイントではないかもしれません
to a need for Microsoft to reassess the
マイクロソフトが再評価する必要性に
way their certificate revocation
証明書の失効方法
procedures hmm that's tough mm-hmm
手順はうーんそれは難しいmm-hmm
because the the part of me wants to say
私の一部が言いたいので
Oh we'll just revoke the certificate
証明書を失効させます
anytime there's an exploit but remember
エクスプロイトがあるときはいつでも
that then that would nullify everybody's
それはすべての人の無効になります
drivers right so this is all mole I mean
ドライバーが正しいので、これは私が意味するすべてのほくろです
as I'm hearing it this is like a new
私はそれを聞いているように、これは新しいようなものです
wave of Trojan attacks so to speak yeah
そう、いわばトロイの木馬攻撃の波
that's what it feels like like you're
それはあなたのように感じるものです
coming in through yeah trusted source to
信頼できるソースを介して
get access is that not the basic
アクセスを取得することは、基本的なことではありません
principle of behind it or is it a whole
その背後にある原理か、それとも全体か
different wave just feels like so
別の波はちょうどそう感じます
they're using it as an elevated
彼らは高架としてそれを使用しています
privilege tactic so they're using a
彼らが使用している特権戦術
driver that windows trusts because of
Windowsが信頼するドライバー
the signature being valid so it's not a
署名が有効であるため、
fake driver it's not like a malware it
偽のドライバー、マルウェアのようではない
is a legitimate driver but it has a bug
正当なドライバーですが、バグがあります
in it mm-hmm that caused it to be
その中にmm-hmmがそれを引き起こした
recalled basically but the Windows
基本的にリコールされましたが、Windows
operating system no matter what version
バージョンに関係なくオペレーティングシステム
you're running still trusts the
あなたはまだ信頼しています
Installer for that driver because of the
そのため、そのドライバーのインストーラー
certificate that is applied to it
それに適用される証明書
and so the hackers are using that to
ハッカーはそれを使って
then be able to elevate their privileges
その後、権限を昇格できる
and do whatever the heck they want and
そして彼らが望むことは何でもします
that's the scary thing because how do
それは怖いことです
you stop that how can you possibly stop
あなたはそれをやめる
that I think it comes down to where's
それはどこにあると思います
your first line of defense I think the
最初の防衛線
only thing you have to that you can look
見ることができるのはあなたが持っていることだけ
at is how did they get in in the first
で、彼らはどのように最初に入りましたか
place
場所
was it a phishing scam was it somebody
フィッシング詐欺でしたか
clicked on an email that had some file
ファイルがあるメールをクリックした
list malware that allowed somebody to
誰かが許可したマルウェアをリストする
run something resident in their computer
コンピューターに常駐する何かを実行する
is it that you have Remote Desktop
リモートデスクトップを持っているということですか
turned on on one of your computers on
コンピューターのいずれかをオンにしました
your network and that's really easy to
あなたのネットワークとそれは本当に簡単です
hack now I don't know how certificates
今、ハッキングする証明書の方法がわからない
work just because I haven't delved into
私が掘り下げていないという理由だけで動作します
that but does each certificate in each
それが、それぞれの各証明書を行います
driver have its own like certificate
ドライバーには独自の証明書があります
identifier no the driver doesn't have
ドライバーが持っていない識別子
its own certificate but the company that
独自の証明書が、その会社
manufactures the driver does so that
ドライバーを製造しているので
certificate says yes to Microsoft this
証明書はこれをMicrosoftにyesと言います
is a gigabyte driver provided by
が提供するギガバイトのドライバーです
gigabyte because it contains the
ギガバイトには
certificate that proves that this is a
これがであることを証明する証明書
legitimate driver from gigabyte so what
ギガバイトの正当なドライバー
if the certificate system changed in
証明書システムが変更された場合
such a way that you have your your main
あなたのメインを持っているような方法
certificate say for gigabyte but then
証明書はギガバイトを言うが、その後
you have your sub certificates for each
それぞれのサブ証明書を持っています
driver roll out so that
ドライバーがロールアウトするように
it identifies this drivers this subset
このドライバー、このサブセットを識別します
yeah developer I feel like that's your
はい、開発者です
you're giving me nightmares right now
あなたは今私に悪夢を与えている
Jeff okay I like where you're going but
ジェフ大丈夫あなたが行くところが好きだけど
it just sounds like a logistical
ロジスティックのように聞こえます
nightmare as far as managing those
それらを管理する限り悪夢
certificates like it could just be a
証明書は
nightmare I think maybe some kind of an
悪夢だと思う
aristocrat is able to identify maybe
貴族は多分識別することができます
it's a checksum that identifies known
それは既知を識別するチェックサムです
faulty drivers or deprecated drivers so
不良ドライバーまたは廃止されたドライバー
that Windows could say yes this is a
Windowsが「はい」と言うことができる
valid certificate however gigabyte has
有効な証明書ですが、ギガバイトには
marked this certificate or this
この証明書またはこれをマーク
installer as bad it's got to be some
インストーラーが悪いので、それはいくつかでなければならない
kind of an identifier yeah that's the
識別子のようなもの
answer
回答
go wonderful big thanks to really Nash
本当にナッシュに素晴らしい大きな感謝を行きます
and our community of viewers for
視聴者のコミュニティ
submitting stories to us this week
今週私たちに物語を提出する
thanks for watching the category-five TV
カテゴリー5のテレビを見てくれてありがとう
newsroom don't forget to Like and
ニュースルームは「いいね」することを忘れないでください
subscribe for all your tech news with a
すべての技術ニュースを購読する
slightly mixed bias and if you
わずかに混合されたバイアスと
appreciate what we do become a patron at
私たちがパトロンになることを感謝します
patreon.com slash newsroom from the
patreon.comは、ニュースルームから
category-five TV newsroom I'm Dasha
カテゴリ5のテレビニュースルーム私はダーシャです
Rickman and I'm Robbie Ferguson thanks
リックマンと私はロビー・ファーガソンです
for being here everybody that is all the
ここにいるのは
time that we have I hope you have had
私たちが持っている時間私はあなたが持っていたことを願っています
fun a good week for you and we look
楽しい一週間をお過ごしください
forward to seeing you again
また会いましょう
[Music]
[音楽]